(this["webpackJsonpnew-app"]=this["webpackJsonpnew-app"]||[]).push([[0],{32:function(t,r,e){},33:function(t,r,e){},44:function(t,r,e){"use strict";e.r(r);var n=e(0),a=e(11),s=e.n(a),c=(e(32),e(12)),i=e(3),o=(e(33),e(1));var u=function(){return Object(o.jsx)(o.Fragment,{children:Object(o.jsx)("nav",{className:"navbars",children:Object(o.jsxs)("div",{className:"navbar-containers",children:[Object(o.jsx)("div",{className:"nav-home",children:Object(o.jsx)(c.b,{to:"/english-learn",children:"Home"})}),Object(o.jsx)("div",{className:"nav-about",children:Object(o.jsx)(c.b,{to:"/about",children:"About"})})]})})})},v=function(){return Object(o.jsxs)("div",{children:[Object(o.jsx)("div",{className:"about-block",children:Object(o.jsx)("p",{children:"\u041f\u0440\u043e\u0433\u0440\u0430\u043c\u043c\u0430 \u0440\u0430\u0441\u0447\u0438\u0442\u0430\u043d\u0430 \u0434\u043b\u044f \u043b\u0438\u0446 \u0438\u0437\u0443\u0447\u0430\u044e\u0449\u0438\u0445 \u0410\u043d\u0433\u043b\u0438\u0439\u0441\u043a\u0438\u0439 \u044f\u0437\u044b\u043a"})}),Object(o.jsx)("div",{className:"footer"})]})},q=function(){return Object(o.jsxs)("div",{children:[Object(o.jsxs)("div",{className:"home",children:[Object(o.jsx)("div",{className:"for-child-block",children:Object(o.jsx)("div",{className:"for-child",children:Object(o.jsx)(c.b,{to:"/startTestsEasy",exact:!0,children:"\u0434\u043b\u044f \u0434\u0435\u0442\u0435\u0439"})})}),Object(o.jsx)("div",{className:"for-profi-block",children:Object(o.jsx)("div",{className:"for-profi",children:Object(o.jsx)(c.b,{to:"/startTestsHard",exact:!0,children:"\u0434\u043b\u044f \u0432\u0437\u0440\u043e\u0441\u043b\u044b\u0445"})})})]}),Object(o.jsx)("div",{className:"footer"})]})},l=e(8),b=e(46),d=function(t){return Object(o.jsxs)("div",{className:"alert alert-success info",role:"alert",children:[Object(o.jsx)("h1",{children:"\u0417\u0430\u0434\u0430\u0447\u0430 \u0432\u044b\u043f\u043e\u043b\u043d\u0435\u043d\u0430!"}),Object(o.jsx)("h2",{children:"\u0412\u044b \u043e\u0442\u0432\u0435\u0442\u0438\u043b\u0438 \u043d\u0430 \u0432\u0441\u0435 \u0432\u043e\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0441\u044b"}),Object(o.jsx)("button",{type:"button",className:"btn btn-outline-success",onClick:function(){t.startTest()},children:"\u041d\u0430\u0447\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0441\u043d\u0430\u0447\u0430\u043b\u0430"})]})},j=function(t){for(var r=[],e=0;e<t;e++)r.push(e);for(var n=[],a=r.length,s=0;a--;)s=Math.floor(Math.random()*(a+1)),n.push(r[s]),r.splice(s,1);return n},h=e(45),m=function(t){for(var r=[0,1,2,3,4],e=[],n=r.length,a=0;n--;)a=Math.floor(Math.random()*(n+1)),e.push(r[a]),r.splice(a,1);for(var s=[],c=0;c<5;c++)s.push(t[e[c]]);return s},O=function(t){var r=Object(n.useState)(t.variantsItem),e=Object(l.a)(r,2),a=e[0],s=e[1],c=Object(n.useState)("btn btn-primary"),i=Object(l.a)(c,2),u=i[0],v=i[1],q=function(){a!==t.correct&&t.live>0?(v("btn btn-danger"),setTimeout(s,500,null)):a!==t.correct&&0===t.live?(v("btn btn-danger"),setTimeout(t.gameOver,500)):(v("btn btn-success"),setTimeout(t.onClick,500))};return Object(o.jsx)(b.a,{in:!!a,classNames:"alert",timeout:300,unmountOnExit:!0,children:Object(o.jsx)("button",{onClick:function(){return q()},className:"".concat(u," btn-variants active"),type:"button",children:a})})},p=function(t){var r=m(t.state.variants).map((function(r,e){return Object(o.jsx)(O,{correct:t.state.correct,live:t.live,gameOver:t.gameOver,onClick:t.onClick,variantsItem:r,ind:e},e)}));return Object(o.jsx)("div",{className:"testComponent",children:Object(o.jsxs)("div",{className:"d-grid gap-3 col-6 mx-auto",children:[Object(o.jsx)("button",{className:"btn btn-dark active questNumber",type:"button",children:t.questNumber}),Object(o.jsx)("button",{className:"btn btn-danger active question",type:"button",children:t.state.question}),r]})})},f=function(t){var r=m(t.state.variants).map((function(r,e){return Object(o.jsx)(O,{correct:t.state.correct,live:t.live,gameOver:t.gameOver,onClick:t.onClick,variantsItem:r,ind:e},e)}));return Object(o.jsx)("div",{className:"testComponent",children:Object(o.jsxs)("div",{className:"d-grid gap-3 col-6 mx-auto",children:[Object(o.jsx)("button",{className:"btn btn-dark active questNumber",type:"button",children:t.questNumber}),Object(o.jsx)("button",{className:"btn btn-danger active question",type:"button",children:t.state.question}),r]})})},g=function(t){var r=Object(n.useState)(!0),e=Object(l.a)(r,2),a=e[0],s=e[1],c=function(){0!==t.finish?(setTimeout(t.nextClick,500),setTimeout(s((function(t){return!t})),1e3)):t.congratulation()};return Object(o.jsx)(o.Fragment,{children:Object(o.jsx)(h.a,{mode:"out-in",children:Object(o.jsx)(b.a,{addEndListener:function(t,r){t.addEventListener("transitionend",r,!1)},classNames:"fade",children:a?Object(o.jsx)(p,{gameOver:t.gameOver,live:t.live,questNumber:t.questNumber,onClick:c,state:t.state}):Object(o.jsx)(f,{gameOver:t.gameOver,live:t.live,questNumber:t.questNumber,onClick:c,state:t.state})},a)})})},x=function(){return[{question:"access",variants:["\u044d\u043a\u0440\u0430\u043d","\u0434\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0443\u043f","\u0443\u0441\u0442\u0440\u043e\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e","\u044f\u0437\u044b\u043a","\u043e\u0442\u043e\u0431\u0440\u0430\u0436\u0430\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u0434\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0443\u043f"},{question:"action",variants:["\u0430\u043a\u0442\u0438\u0432","\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043c\u0435\u0442","\u0432\u043d\u0438\u043c\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0435","\u043c\u0430\u0433\u0430\u0437\u0438\u043d"],correct:"\u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0435"},{question:"application",variants:["\u043f\u0440\u0438\u043b\u043e\u0436\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u0434\u043e\u043f\u043e\u043b\u043d\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u0438\u0437\u043c\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0432\u044b\u0440\u0435\u0437\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043f\u043e\u043b\u0443\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u043f\u0440\u0438\u043b\u043e\u0436\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435"},{question:"building",variants:["\u043f\u0435\u0440\u0441\u043e\u043d\u0430\u0436","\u0432\u0432\u0435\u0434\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u0441\u043f\u0443\u0441\u0442\u044f","\u0441\u0442\u0440\u043e\u0438\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e","\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043c\u0435\u0442"],correct:"\u0441\u0442\u0440\u043e\u0438\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e"},{question:"cancel",variants:["\u0441\u043e\u0437\u0434\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043e\u0442\u043c\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0441\u043e\u0433\u043b\u0430\u0441\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0437\u0430\u043a\u0440\u044b\u0442\u044c","\u043e\u0442\u0434\u0430\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u043e\u0442\u043c\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0442\u044c"},{question:"with",variants:["\u043d\u0430","\u0432","\u0441","\u0438\u0437","\u0434\u043b\u044f"],correct:"\u0441"},{question:"open",variants:["c\u043e\u0437\u0434\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043e\u0442\u043c\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0441\u043e\u0433\u043b\u0430\u0441\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043e\u0442\u043a\u0440\u044b\u0442\u044c","\u043e\u0442\u0434\u0430\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u043e\u0442\u043a\u0440\u044b\u0442\u044c"},{question:"close",variants:["\u0441\u043e\u0437\u0434\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043e\u0442\u043c\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0441\u043e\u0433\u043b\u0430\u0441\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0437\u0430\u043a\u0440\u044b\u0442\u044c","\u043e\u0442\u0434\u0430\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u0437\u0430\u043a\u0440\u044b\u0442\u044c"},{question:"error",variants:["\u043f\u043e\u0438\u0441\u043a","\u043e\u0448\u0438\u0431\u043a\u0430","\u0443\u0441\u043f\u0435\u0448\u043d\u043e","\u0432\u0437\u044f\u0442\u044c","\u043e\u0442\u0434\u0430\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u043e\u0448\u0438\u0431\u043a\u0430"},{question:"store",variants:["\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043c\u0435\u0442","\u0440\u0443\u0447\u043a\u0430","\u0445\u0440\u0430\u043d\u0438\u043b\u0438\u0449\u0435","\u0447\u0438\u0441\u0442\u0438\u043b\u0438\u0449\u0435","\u043a\u043b\u0443\u0431"],correct:"\u0445\u0440\u0430\u043d\u0438\u043b\u0438\u0449\u0435"},{question:"item",variants:["\u0432\u043a\u043b\u044e\u0447\u0430\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c","\u0430\u043c\u0443\u043b\u0435\u0442","\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043c\u0435\u0442","\u0441\u043b\u043e\u0432\u043e","\u0431\u0443\u043a\u0432\u0430"],correct:"\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043c\u0435\u0442"},{question:"type",variants:["\u0442\u0443\u043d\u043d\u0435\u043b\u044c","\u0432\u0438\u0434","\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0445\u043e\u0434","\u0441\u0435\u043a\u0440\u0435\u0442","\u0442\u0438\u043f"],correct:"\u0442\u0438\u043f"},{question:"page",variants:["\u0444\u0430\u0439\u043b","\u043f\u0430\u043f\u043a\u0430","\u0445\u0440\u0430\u043d\u0438\u043b\u0438\u0449\u0435","\u0441\u0442\u0440\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0446\u0430","\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043c\u0435\u0442"],correct:"\u0441\u0442\u0440\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0446\u0430"},{question:"delete",variants:["\u0443\u0434\u0430\u043b\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u043e\u0442\u043c\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0441\u043e\u0433\u043b\u0430\u0441\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043e\u0442\u043a\u0440\u044b\u0442\u044c","\u043e\u0442\u0434\u0430\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u0443\u0434\u0430\u043b\u0438\u0442\u044c"},{question:"state",variants:["\u0430\u043a\u0442\u0438\u0432","\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043c\u0435\u0442","\u0432\u043d\u0438\u043c\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0435","\u0441\u043e\u0441\u0442\u043e\u044f\u043d\u0438\u0435"],correct:"\u0441\u043e\u0441\u0442\u043e\u044f\u043d\u0438\u0435"},{question:"default",variants:["\u043f\u0430\u0434\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u043f\u043e\u0434\u044a\u0435\u043c","\u043f\u043e \u0446\u0435\u043d\u0442\u0440\u0443","\u043f\u043e \u0443\u043c\u043e\u043b\u0447\u0430\u043d\u0438\u044e","\u043c\u0435\u0440\u043e\u043f\u0440\u0438\u044f\u0442\u0438\u0435"],correct:"\u043f\u043e \u0443\u043c\u043e\u043b\u0447\u0430\u043d\u0438\u044e"},{question:"return",variants:["\u0432\u043e\u0437\u0432\u0440\u0430\u0449\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043e\u0442\u043c\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0441\u043e\u0433\u043b\u0430\u0441\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043e\u0442\u043a\u0440\u044b\u0442\u044c","\u043f\u043e\u043b\u0443\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u0432\u043e\u0437\u0432\u0440\u0430\u0449\u0430\u0442\u044c"},{question:"warning",variants:["\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u0443\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0436\u0434\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u043f\u043e\u0434\u0434\u0435\u0440\u0436\u043a\u0430","\u043f\u043e\u043c\u043e\u0449\u044c","\u043f\u043e\u0438\u0441\u043a","\u0438\u0441\u0445\u043e\u0434\u043d\u044b\u0439"],correct:"\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u0443\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0436\u0434\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435"},{question:"danger",variants:["\u043e\u043f\u0430\u0441\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c","\u043f\u043e\u0434\u0434\u0435\u0440\u0436\u043a\u0430","\u043f\u043e\u043c\u043e\u0449\u044c","\u043f\u043e\u0438\u0441\u043a","\u0438\u0441\u0445\u043e\u0434\u043d\u044b\u0439"],correct:"\u043e\u043f\u0430\u0441\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c"},{question:"success",variants:["\u0443\u0441\u043f\u0435\u0445","\u043f\u043e\u0434\u0434\u0435\u0440\u0436\u043a\u0430","\u043f\u043e\u043c\u043e\u0449\u044c","\u043f\u043e\u0438\u0441\u043a","\u0438\u0441\u0445\u043e\u0434\u043d\u044b\u0439"],correct:"\u0443\u0441\u043f\u0435\u0445"},{question:"exact",variants:["\u0442\u043e\u0447\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u043f\u043e\u0434\u0434\u0435\u0440\u0436\u043a\u0430","\u043a\u043e\u0440\u043e\u0442\u043a\u0438\u0439","\u043f\u043e\u0438\u0441\u043a","\u0438\u0441\u0445\u043e\u0434\u043d\u044b\u0439"],correct:"\u0442\u043e\u0447\u043d\u044b\u0439"},{question:"search",variants:["\u0442\u043e\u0447\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u043f\u043e\u0434\u0434\u0435\u0440\u0436\u043a\u0430","\u043a\u043e\u0440\u043e\u0442\u043a\u0438\u0439","\u043f\u043e\u0438\u0441\u043a","\u0438\u0441\u0445\u043e\u0434\u043d\u044b\u0439"],correct:"\u043f\u043e\u0438\u0441\u043a"},{question:"source",variants:["\u0442\u043e\u0447\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u043f\u043e\u0434\u0434\u0435\u0440\u0436\u043a\u0430","\u043a\u043e\u0440\u043e\u0442\u043a\u0438\u0439","\u043f\u043e\u0438\u0441\u043a","\u0438\u0441\u0445\u043e\u0434\u043d\u044b\u0439"],correct:"\u0438\u0441\u0445\u043e\u0434\u043d\u044b\u0439"},{question:"copy",variants:["\u043a\u043e\u043d\u0444\u0435\u0442\u0430","\u043e\u0431\u0435\u0440\u0442\u043a\u0430","\u043a\u043e\u043f\u0438\u0440\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043f\u0435\u0447\u0430\u0442\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0432\u044b\u0440\u0435\u0437\u0430\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u043a\u043e\u043f\u0438\u0440\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c"},{question:"cut",variants:["\u043a\u043e\u043d\u0444\u0435\u0442\u0430","\u043e\u0431\u0435\u0440\u0442\u043a\u0430","\u043a\u043e\u043f\u0438\u0440\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043f\u0435\u0447\u0430\u0442\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0432\u044b\u0440\u0435\u0437\u0430\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u0432\u044b\u0440\u0435\u0437\u0430\u0442\u044c"},{question:"paste",variants:["\u0432\u0441\u0442\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u043e\u0431\u0435\u0440\u0442\u043a\u0430","\u043a\u043e\u043f\u0438\u0440\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043f\u0435\u0447\u0430\u0442\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0432\u044b\u0440\u0435\u0437\u0430\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u0432\u0441\u0442\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0442\u044c"},{question:"print",variants:["\u0432\u0441\u0442\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u043e\u0431\u0435\u0440\u0442\u043a\u0430","\u043a\u043e\u043f\u0438\u0440\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043f\u0435\u0447\u0430\u0442\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0432\u044b\u0440\u0435\u0437\u0430\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u043f\u0435\u0447\u0430\u0442\u0430\u0442\u044c"},{question:"edit",variants:["\u0432\u0441\u0442\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0440\u0435\u0434\u0430\u043a\u0442\u0438\u0440\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0435\u0434\u0438\u043d\u0438\u0446\u0430","\u043f\u0435\u0447\u0430\u0442\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0432\u044b\u0440\u0435\u0437\u0430\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u0440\u0435\u0434\u0430\u043a\u0442\u0438\u0440\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c"},{question:"data",variants:["\u0434\u0430\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0435","\u0434\u0430\u0442\u0430","\u0432\u0440\u0435\u043c\u044f","\u0447\u0430\u0441\u044b","\u043c\u0435\u0441\u044f\u0446"],correct:"\u0434\u0430\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0435"},{question:"date",variants:["\u0434\u0430\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0435","\u0434\u0430\u0442\u0430","\u0432\u0440\u0435\u043c\u044f","\u0447\u0430\u0441\u044b","\u043c\u0435\u0441\u044f\u0446"],correct:"\u0434\u0430\u0442\u0430"},{question:"time",variants:["\u0434\u0430\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0435","\u0434\u0430\u0442\u0430","\u0432\u0440\u0435\u043c\u044f","\u0447\u0430\u0441\u044b","\u043c\u0435\u0441\u044f\u0446"],correct:"\u0432\u0440\u0435\u043c\u044f"},{question:"year",variants:["\u0433\u043e\u0434","\u0434\u0430\u0442\u0430","\u0432\u0440\u0435\u043c\u044f","\u0447\u0430\u0441\u044b","\u043c\u0435\u0441\u044f\u0446"],correct:"\u0433\u043e\u0434"},{question:"month",variants:["\u0433\u043e\u0434","\u0434\u0430\u0442\u0430","\u0432\u0440\u0435\u043c\u044f","\u0447\u0430\u0441\u044b","\u043c\u0435\u0441\u044f\u0446"],correct:"\u043c\u0435\u0441\u044f\u0446"},{question:"week",variants:["\u0433\u043e\u0434","\u043d\u0435\u0434\u0435\u043b\u044f","\u0432\u0440\u0435\u043c\u044f","\u0447\u0430\u0441\u044b","\u043c\u0435\u0441\u044f\u0446"],correct:"\u043d\u0435\u0434\u0435\u043b\u044f"},{question:"view",variants:["\u0432\u0438\u0434","\u043c\u043e\u0434\u0435\u043b\u044c","\u043c\u0430\u0440\u043a\u0430","\u0434\u0438\u0437\u0430\u0439\u043d","\u0441\u043a\u043b\u0430\u0434"],correct:"\u0432\u0438\u0434"},{question:"show",variants:["\u043f\u043e\u043a\u0430\u0437\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0441\u043a\u0440\u044b\u0442\u044c","\u043c\u0430\u0440\u043a\u0430","\u0434\u0438\u0437\u0430\u0439\u043d","\u0441\u043a\u043b\u0430\u0434"],correct:"\u043f\u043e\u043a\u0430\u0437\u0430\u0442\u044c"},{question:"hide",variants:["\u043f\u043e\u043a\u0430\u0437\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0441\u043a\u0440\u044b\u0442\u044c","\u043c\u0430\u0440\u043a\u0430","\u0434\u0438\u0437\u0430\u0439\u043d","\u0441\u043a\u043b\u0430\u0434"],correct:"\u0441\u043a\u0440\u044b\u0442\u044c"},{question:"button",variants:["\u043a\u043d\u043e\u043f\u043a\u0430","\u0445\u043b\u0435\u0431","\u0431\u0430\u0442\u043e\u043d","\u0442\u043e\u043b\u0441\u0442\u044b\u0439","\u043d\u0430\u0436\u0430\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u043a\u043d\u043e\u043f\u043a\u0430"},{question:"press",variants:["\u043a\u043d\u043e\u043f\u043a\u0430","\u0445\u043b\u0435\u0431","\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0441\u0441\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0442\u043e\u043b\u0441\u0442\u044b\u0439","\u043d\u0430\u0436\u0430\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u043d\u0430\u0436\u0430\u0442\u044c"},{question:"display",variants:["\u044d\u043a\u0440\u0430\u043d","\u043e\u043a\u043d\u043e","\u0434\u0438\u0441\u043a\u043e\u043d\u0442","\u0434\u0438\u0441\u043a","\u043e\u0442\u043e\u0431\u0440\u0430\u0436\u0430\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u043e\u0442\u043e\u0431\u0440\u0430\u0436\u0430\u0442\u044c"},{question:"screen",variants:["\u044d\u043a\u0440\u0430\u043d","\u043e\u043a\u043d\u043e","\u0434\u0438\u0441\u043a\u043e\u043d\u0442","\u0434\u0438\u0441\u043a","\u0441\u0435\u043d\u0441\u043e\u0440"],correct:"\u044d\u043a\u0440\u0430\u043d"},{question:"developer",variants:["\u0445\u043e\u043b\u0434\u0438\u043d\u0433","\u0440\u0430\u0437\u0440\u0430\u0431\u043e\u0442\u0447\u0438\u043a","\u0441\u043f\u0435\u0446\u0438\u0430\u043b\u0438\u0441\u0442","\u0441\u043f\u0435\u0446\u0438\u0438","\u043a\u043e\u043d\u0441\u0442\u0440\u0443\u043a\u0442\u043e\u0440"],correct:"\u0440\u0430\u0437\u0440\u0430\u0431\u043e\u0442\u0447\u0438\u043a"},{question:"clerk",variants:["\u0446\u0438\u0440\u043a","\u0446\u0438\u0440\u043a\u0443\u043b\u044c","\u0441\u043b\u0443\u0436\u0430\u0449\u0438\u0439","\u0443\u0431\u043e\u0440\u0449\u0438\u043a","\u043a\u043e\u043d\u0441\u0442\u0440\u0443\u043a\u0442\u043e\u0440"],correct:"\u0441\u043b\u0443\u0436\u0430\u0449\u0438\u0439"},{question:"employee",variants:["\u0440\u0430\u0431\u043e\u0442\u043d\u0438\u043a","\u0440\u0430\u0437\u0440\u0430\u0431\u043e\u0442\u0447\u0438\u043a","\u0441\u043f\u0435\u0446\u0438\u0430\u043b\u0438\u0441\u0442","\u043f\u0443\u0441\u0442\u043e\u0439","\u043a\u043e\u043d\u0441\u0442\u0440\u0443\u043a\u0442\u043e\u0440"],correct:"\u0440\u0430\u0431\u043e\u0442\u043d\u0438\u043a"},{question:"empty",variants:["\u043f\u043e\u043b\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0441\u0442\u043e\u0439","\u0432\u044b\u0441\u043e\u043a\u0438\u0439","\u043f\u0443\u0441\u0442\u043e\u0439","\u0445\u0443\u0434\u043e\u0439"],correct:"\u043f\u0443\u0441\u0442\u043e\u0439"},{question:"follow",variants:["\u0441\u043b\u0435\u0434\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043f\u043e\u043b\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u043f\u043b\u0430\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043f\u0443\u0441\u0442\u043e\u0439","\u0445\u0443\u0434\u043e\u0439"],correct:"\u0441\u043b\u0435\u0434\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c"},{question:"net",variants:["\u043d\u0435\u0442","\u0441\u0435\u0442\u044c","\u0441\u0432\u044f\u0437\u044c","\u043f\u0430\u043a\u0435\u0442","\u043e\u043f\u0435\u0440\u0430\u0442\u043e\u0440"],correct:"\u0441\u0435\u0442\u044c"},{question:"setup",variants:["\u043d\u0430\u0441\u0442\u0440\u043e\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u043f\u043e\u0434\u043d\u044f\u0442\u044c","\u0434\u0430\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0435","\u043e\u0442\u043a\u043b\u044e\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0432\u043a\u043b\u044e\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u043d\u0430\u0441\u0442\u0440\u043e\u0438\u0442\u044c"},{question:"option",variants:["\u043d\u0430\u0441\u0442\u0440\u043e\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0432\u0430\u0440\u0438\u0430\u043d\u0442","\u0434\u0430\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0435","\u043e\u0442\u043a\u043b\u044e\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0432\u043a\u043b\u044e\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u0432\u0430\u0440\u0438\u0430\u043d\u0442"},{question:"get",variants:["\u0432\u043e\u0437\u0432\u0440\u0430\u0449\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043e\u0442\u043c\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0441\u043e\u0433\u043b\u0430\u0441\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043e\u0442\u043a\u0440\u044b\u0442\u044c","\u043f\u043e\u043b\u0443\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u043f\u043e\u043b\u0443\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044c"},{question:"give",variants:["\u0432\u043e\u0437\u0432\u0440\u0430\u0449\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043e\u0442\u043c\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0441\u043e\u0433\u043b\u0430\u0441\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043e\u0442\u0434\u0430\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043f\u043e\u043b\u0443\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u043e\u0442\u0434\u0430\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c"},{question:"run",variants:["\u0432\u043e\u0437\u0432\u0440\u0430\u0449\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0437\u0430\u043f\u0443\u0441\u0442\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0441\u043e\u0433\u043b\u0430\u0441\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043e\u0442\u0434\u0430\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043f\u043e\u043b\u0443\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u0437\u0430\u043f\u0443\u0441\u0442\u0438\u0442\u044c"},{question:"download",variants:["\u0432\u043e\u0437\u0432\u0440\u0430\u0449\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0437\u0430\u043f\u0443\u0441\u0442\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0441\u043a\u0430\u0447\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043e\u0442\u0434\u0430\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043f\u043e\u043b\u0443\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u0441\u043a\u0430\u0447\u0430\u0442\u044c"},{question:"install",variants:["\u0443\u0441\u0442\u0430\u043d\u043e\u0432\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0437\u0430\u043f\u0443\u0441\u0442\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0441\u043a\u0430\u0447\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043e\u0442\u0434\u0430\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043f\u043e\u043b\u0443\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u0443\u0441\u0442\u0430\u043d\u043e\u0432\u0438\u0442\u044c"},{question:"check",variants:["\u0443\u0441\u0442\u0430\u043d\u043e\u0432\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0437\u0430\u043f\u0443\u0441\u0442\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0441\u043a\u0430\u0447\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0432\u0435\u0440\u044f\u0442\u044c","\u043f\u043e\u043b\u0443\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0432\u0435\u0440\u044f\u0442\u044c"},{question:"pay",variants:["\u0443\u0441\u0442\u0430\u043d\u043e\u0432\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0437\u0430\u043f\u0443\u0441\u0442\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0441\u043a\u0430\u0447\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0432\u0435\u0440\u044f\u0442\u044c","\u043e\u043f\u043b\u0430\u0442\u0438\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u043e\u043f\u043b\u0430\u0442\u0438\u0442\u044c"},{question:"word",variants:["\u0440\u0430\u0431\u043e\u0442\u0430","\u0441\u043b\u043e\u0432\u043e","\u0445\u0440\u0430\u043d\u0438\u043b\u0438\u0449\u0435","\u0441\u0442\u0440\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0446\u0430","\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043c\u0435\u0442"],correct:"\u0441\u043b\u043e\u0432\u043e"},{question:"letter",variants:["\u0431\u0443\u043a\u0432\u0430","\u0441\u043b\u043e\u0432\u043e","\u0441\u043f\u0443\u0441\u0442\u044f","\u043a\u043d\u0438\u0433\u0430","\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043c\u0435\u0442"],correct:"\u0431\u0443\u043a\u0432\u0430"},{question:"later",variants:["\u0431\u0443\u043a\u0432\u0430","\u0441\u043b\u043e\u0432\u043e","\u0441\u043f\u0443\u0441\u0442\u044f","\u043a\u043d\u0438\u0433\u0430","\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043c\u0435\u0442"],correct:"\u0441\u043f\u0443\u0441\u0442\u044f"},{question:"character",variants:["\u043f\u0435\u0440\u0441\u043e\u043d\u0430\u0436","\u0434\u0432\u0438\u0433\u0430\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c","\u0441\u043f\u0443\u0441\u0442\u044f","\u043a\u043d\u0438\u0433\u0430","\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043c\u0435\u0442"],correct:"\u043f\u0435\u0440\u0441\u043e\u043d\u0430\u0436"},{question:"tutorial",variants:["\u043f\u0435\u0440\u0441\u043e\u043d\u0430\u0436","\u0432\u0432\u0435\u0434\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u0441\u043f\u0443\u0441\u0442\u044f","\u043a\u043d\u0438\u0433\u0430","\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043c\u0435\u0442"],correct:"\u0432\u0432\u0435\u0434\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435"},{question:"community",variants:["\u043f\u0435\u0440\u0441\u043e\u043d\u0430\u0436","\u0432\u0432\u0435\u0434\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u0441\u043e\u043e\u0431\u0449\u0435\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e","\u043a\u043d\u0438\u0433\u0430","\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043c\u0435\u0442"],correct:"\u0441\u043e\u043e\u0431\u0449\u0435\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e"},{question:"take",variants:["\u0432\u043e\u0437\u0432\u0440\u0430\u0449\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0431\u0440\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0441\u043e\u0433\u043b\u0430\u0441\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043e\u0442\u043a\u0440\u044b\u0442\u044c","\u043f\u043e\u043b\u0443\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u0431\u0440\u0430\u0442\u044c"},{question:"create",variants:["\u0432\u043e\u0437\u0432\u0440\u0430\u0449\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0431\u0440\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0441\u043e\u0433\u043b\u0430\u0441\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0441\u043e\u0437\u0434\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043f\u043e\u043b\u0443\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u0441\u043e\u0437\u0434\u0430\u0442\u044c"},{question:"image",variants:["\u043f\u0440\u0438\u043b\u043e\u0436\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u0434\u043e\u043f\u043e\u043b\u043d\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u0438\u0437\u043c\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0432\u044b\u0440\u0435\u0437\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0438\u0437\u043e\u0431\u0440\u0430\u0436\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435"],correct:"\u0438\u0437\u043e\u0431\u0440\u0430\u0436\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435"},{question:"change",variants:["\u043f\u0440\u0438\u043b\u043e\u0436\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u0434\u043e\u043f\u043e\u043b\u043d\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u0438\u0437\u043c\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0432\u044b\u0440\u0435\u0437\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0438\u0437\u043e\u0431\u0440\u0430\u0436\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435"],correct:"\u0438\u0437\u043c\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0442\u044c"},{question:"exchange",variants:["\u043e\u0431\u043c\u0435\u043d","\u0434\u043e\u043f\u043e\u043b\u043d\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u0438\u0437\u043c\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0432\u044b\u0440\u0435\u0437\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0438\u0437\u043e\u0431\u0440\u0430\u0436\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435"],correct:"\u043e\u0431\u043c\u0435\u043d"},{question:"folder",variants:["\u0444\u0430\u0439\u043b","\u043f\u0430\u043f\u043a\u0430","\u0445\u0440\u0430\u043d\u0438\u043b\u0438\u0449\u0435","\u0441\u0442\u0440\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0446\u0430","\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043c\u0435\u0442"],correct:"\u043f\u0430\u043f\u043a\u0430"},{question:"save",variants:["\u043e\u0431\u043c\u0435\u043d","\u0434\u043e\u043f\u043e\u043b\u043d\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u0438\u0437\u043c\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0432\u044b\u0440\u0435\u0437\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0441\u043e\u0445\u0440\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u0441\u043e\u0445\u0440\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0442\u044c"},{question:"user",variants:["\u043f\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0437\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c","\u0440\u0430\u0437\u0440\u0430\u0431\u043e\u0442\u0447\u0438\u043a","\u0441\u043f\u0435\u0446\u0438\u0430\u043b\u0438\u0441\u0442","\u0441\u043f\u0435\u0446\u0438\u0438","\u043a\u043e\u043d\u0441\u0442\u0440\u0443\u043a\u0442\u043e\u0440"],correct:"\u043f\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0437\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c"},{question:"difficult",variants:["\u043b\u0435\u0433\u043a\u0438\u0439","\u0442\u0440\u0443\u0434\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0441\u0442\u043e\u0439","\u043e\u0442\u043a\u0440\u044b\u0442\u044b\u0439","\u0437\u0430\u043a\u0440\u044b\u0442\u044b\u0439"],correct:"\u0442\u0440\u0443\u0434\u043d\u044b\u0439"},{question:"hard",variants:["\u043b\u0435\u0433\u043a\u0438\u0439","\u0436\u0435\u0441\u0442\u043a\u0438\u0439","\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0441\u0442\u043e\u0439","\u043e\u0442\u043a\u0440\u044b\u0442\u044b\u0439","\u0437\u0430\u043a\u0440\u044b\u0442\u044b\u0439"],correct:"\u0436\u0435\u0441\u0442\u043a\u0438\u0439"},{question:"easy",variants:["\u043b\u0435\u0433\u043a\u0438\u0439","\u0436\u0435\u0441\u0442\u043a\u0438\u0439","\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0441\u0442\u043e\u0439","\u043e\u0442\u043a\u0440\u044b\u0442\u044b\u0439","\u0437\u0430\u043a\u0440\u044b\u0442\u044b\u0439"],correct:"\u043b\u0435\u0433\u043a\u0438\u0439"},{question:"guest",variants:["\u043f\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0437\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c","\u0440\u0430\u0437\u0440\u0430\u0431\u043e\u0442\u0447\u0438\u043a","\u0441\u043f\u0435\u0446\u0438\u0430\u043b\u0438\u0441\u0442","\u0433\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c","\u043a\u043e\u043d\u0441\u0442\u0440\u0443\u043a\u0442\u043e\u0440"],correct:"\u0433\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c"},{question:"device",variants:["\u044d\u043a\u0440\u0430\u043d","\u043e\u043a\u043d\u043e","\u0443\u0441\u0442\u0440\u043e\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e","\u0434\u0438\u0441\u043a","\u043e\u0442\u043e\u0431\u0440\u0430\u0436\u0430\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u0443\u0441\u0442\u0440\u043e\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e"},{question:"language",variants:["\u044d\u043a\u0440\u0430\u043d","\u043e\u043a\u043d\u043e","\u0443\u0441\u0442\u0440\u043e\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e","\u044f\u0437\u044b\u043a","\u043e\u0442\u043e\u0431\u0440\u0430\u0436\u0430\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u044f\u0437\u044b\u043a"},{question:"send",variants:["\u043e\u0442\u043f\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0434\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0443\u043f","\u0443\u0441\u0442\u0440\u043e\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e","\u044f\u0437\u044b\u043a","\u043e\u0442\u043e\u0431\u0440\u0430\u0436\u0430\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u043e\u0442\u043f\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0442\u044c"},{question:"if",variants:["\u0435\u0441\u043b\u0438","\u0447\u0442\u043e","\u043a\u0430\u043a","\u0438\u043d\u0430\u0447\u0435","\u0435\u0449\u0435"],correct:"\u0435\u0441\u043b\u0438"},{question:"else",variants:["\u0435\u0441\u043b\u0438","\u0447\u0442\u043e","\u043a\u0430\u043a","\u0438\u043d\u0430\u0447\u0435","\u0435\u0449\u0435"],correct:"\u0438\u043d\u0430\u0447\u0435"},{question:"more",variants:["\u043c\u043e\u0440\u0435","\u0431\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0448\u0435","\u043e\u0437\u0435\u0440\u043e","\u0441\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043d\u0438\u0439","\u043c\u0430\u0441\u043b\u043e"],correct:"\u0431\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0448\u0435"},{question:"have",variants:["\u0438\u043c\u0435\u0442\u044c","\u0436\u0435\u043b\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0431\u0440\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0445\u043e\u0442\u0435\u0442\u044c","\u0432\u0435\u0440\u043d\u0443\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u0438\u043c\u0435\u0442\u044c"},{question:"it",variants:["\u044d\u0442\u043e","\u0442\u0430\u043c","\u0432","\u0441","\u043a\u0430\u043a"],correct:"\u044d\u0442\u043e"},{question:"as",variants:["\u0432 \u0432\u0438\u0434\u0435","\u043d\u0430\u0448","\u0438\u0445","\u0440\u044f\u0434\u043e\u043c","\u0441\u043e\u0433\u043b\u0430\u0441\u0438\u0435"],correct:"\u0432 \u0432\u0438\u0434\u0435"},{question:"add",variants:["\u0434\u043e\u0431\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0438\u0437\u043c\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0443\u0431\u0440\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0441\u043b\u043e\u043c\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043e\u0442\u043a\u0440\u044b\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u0434\u043e\u0431\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0442\u044c"},{question:"for",variants:["\u0434\u043b\u044f","\u043d\u0430\u0448","\u0438\u0445","\u0441","\u0432\u0430\u0448"],correct:"\u0434\u043b\u044f"},{question:"while",variants:["\u043f\u043e\u043a\u0430","\u0434\u043b\u044f","\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0449\u0430\u0439","\u0436\u0430\u043b\u044c","\u0441\u043e\u0433\u043b\u0430\u0441\u0438\u0435"],correct:"\u043f\u043e\u043a\u0430"},{question:"that",variants:["\u0447\u0442\u043e","\u0435\u0441\u043b\u0438","\u043a\u0430\u043a","\u0433\u0434\u0435","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u0447\u0442\u043e"},{question:"on",variants:["\u043d\u0430","\u043e\u0442","\u0432","\u0441","\u0447\u0442\u043e"],correct:"\u043d\u0430"},{question:"do",variants:["\u0434\u0435\u043b\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0432\u0437\u044f\u0442\u044c","\u0443\u0439\u0442\u0438","\u0432\u043e\u0439\u0442\u0438","\u0441\u043e\u0433\u043b\u0430\u0441\u0438\u0435"],correct:"\u0434\u0435\u043b\u0430\u0442\u044c"},{question:"say",variants:["\u0441\u043a\u0430\u0437\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0432\u0437\u044f\u0442\u044c","\u0443\u0439\u0442\u0438","\u0432\u043e\u0439\u0442\u0438","\u0441\u043e\u0433\u043b\u0430\u0441\u0438\u0435"],correct:"\u0441\u043a\u0430\u0437\u0430\u0442\u044c"},{question:"from",variants:["\u0438\u0437","\u043d\u0430","\u0432","\u043a\u0430\u043a","\u0447\u0442\u043e"],correct:"\u0438\u0437"},{question:"by",variants:["\u043d\u0430","\u043e\u0442","\u0432","\u0441","\u0447\u0442\u043e"],correct:"\u043e\u0442"},{question:"or",variants:["\u0438\u043b\u0438","\u043e\u0442","\u0432","\u0441","\u0447\u0442\u043e"],correct:"\u0438\u043b\u0438"},{question:"would",variants:["\u0431\u044b","\u0435\u0441\u043b\u0438","\u043a\u0430\u043a","\u0433\u0434\u0435","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u0431\u044b"},{question:"all",variants:["\u0432\u0441\u0435","\u0435\u0441\u043b\u0438","\u043a\u0430\u043a","\u0433\u0434\u0435","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u0432\u0441\u0435"},{question:"about",variants:["\u043e\u0431","\u0435\u0441\u043b\u0438","\u043a\u0430\u043a","\u0433\u0434\u0435","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u043e\u0431"},{question:"which",variants:["\u043a\u043e\u0442\u043e\u0440\u044b\u0439","\u0435\u0441\u043b\u0438","\u043a\u0430\u043a","\u0433\u0434\u0435","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u043a\u043e\u0442\u043e\u0440\u044b\u0439"},{question:"into",variants:["\u043a\u043e\u0442\u043e\u0440\u044b\u0439","\u0432\u043d\u0443\u0442\u0440\u0438","\u043a\u0430\u043a","\u0433\u0434\u0435","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u0432\u043d\u0443\u0442\u0440\u0438"},{question:"could",variants:["\u043c\u043e\u0433","\u0435\u0441\u043b\u0438","\u043a\u0430\u043a","\u0433\u0434\u0435","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u043c\u043e\u0433"},{question:"now",variants:["\u043c\u043e\u0433","\u0441\u0435\u0439\u0447\u0430\u0441","\u043a\u0430\u043a","\u0433\u0434\u0435","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u0441\u0435\u0439\u0447\u0430\u0441"},{question:"other",variants:["\u043c\u043e\u0433","\u0434\u0440\u0443\u0433\u043e\u0439","\u043e\u0442\u0435\u0446","\u0434\u0435\u0434","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u0434\u0440\u0443\u0433\u043e\u0439"},{question:"want",variants:["\u0438\u043c\u0435\u0442\u044c","\u0438\u0441\u043a\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0431\u0440\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0445\u043e\u0442\u0435\u0442\u044c","\u0432\u0435\u0440\u043d\u0443\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u0445\u043e\u0442\u0435\u0442\u044c"},{question:"way",variants:["\u0441\u043f\u043e\u0441\u043e\u0431","\u0435\u0441\u043b\u0438","\u043a\u0430\u043a","\u0433\u0434\u0435","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u0441\u043f\u043e\u0441\u043e\u0431"},{question:"first",variants:["\u043f\u0435\u0440\u0432\u044b\u0439","\u043f\u043e\u0442\u043e\u043c\u0443 \u0447\u0442\u043e","\u043f\u043e\u043a\u0430","\u0433\u0434\u0435","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u043f\u0435\u0440\u0432\u044b\u0439"},{question:"because",variants:["\u043f\u0435\u0440\u0432\u044b\u0439","\u043f\u043e\u0442\u043e\u043c\u0443 \u0447\u0442\u043e","\u043f\u043e\u043a\u0430","\u0433\u0434\u0435","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u043f\u043e\u0442\u043e\u043c\u0443 \u0447\u0442\u043e"},{question:"also",variants:["\u043f\u0435\u0440\u0432\u044b\u0439","\u043f\u043e\u0442\u043e\u043c\u0443 \u0447\u0442\u043e","\u043f\u043e\u043a\u0430","\u0442\u0430\u043a\u0436\u0435","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u0442\u0430\u043a\u0436\u0435"},{question:"find",variants:["\u043d\u0430\u0445\u043e\u0434\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u043f\u043e\u0442\u043e\u043c\u0443 \u0447\u0442\u043e","\u043f\u043e\u043a\u0430","\u0442\u0430\u043a\u0436\u0435","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u043d\u0430\u0445\u043e\u0434\u0438\u0442\u044c"},{question:"many",variants:["\u043c\u043e\u0440\u0435","\u043c\u043d\u043e\u0433\u043e","\u043e\u0437\u0435\u0440\u043e","\u0441\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043d\u0438\u0439","\u043c\u0430\u0441\u043b\u043e"],correct:"\u043c\u043d\u043e\u0433\u043e"},{question:"well",variants:["\u0441\u043f\u043e\u0441\u043e\u0431","\u0435\u0441\u043b\u0438","\u043a\u0430\u043a","\u0445\u043e\u0440\u043e\u0448\u043e","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u0445\u043e\u0440\u043e\u0448\u043e"},{question:"only",variants:["\u0442\u043e\u043b\u044c\u043a\u043e","\u0435\u0441\u043b\u0438","\u043a\u0430\u043a","\u0445\u043e\u0440\u043e\u0448\u043e","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u0442\u043e\u043b\u044c\u043a\u043e"},{question:"even",variants:["\u0434\u0430\u0436\u0435","\u0435\u0441\u043b\u0438","\u043a\u0430\u043a","\u0433\u0434\u0435","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u0434\u0430\u0436\u0435"},{question:"back",variants:["\u043f\u0435\u0440\u0432\u044b\u0439","\u043f\u043e\u0442\u043e\u043c\u0443 \u0447\u0442\u043e","\u043d\u0430\u0437\u0430\u0434","\u0442\u0430\u043a\u0436\u0435","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u043d\u0430\u0437\u0430\u0434"},{question:"any",variants:["\u043b\u044e\u0431\u043e\u0439","\u043f\u043e\u0442\u043e\u043c\u0443 \u0447\u0442\u043e","\u043d\u0430\u0437\u0430\u0434","\u0442\u0430\u043a\u0436\u0435","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u043b\u044e\u0431\u043e\u0439"},{question:"after",variants:["\u043f\u0435\u0440\u0432\u044b\u0439","\u043f\u043e\u0442\u043e\u043c\u0443 \u0447\u0442\u043e","\u043f\u043e\u043a\u0430","\u043f\u043e\u0441\u043b\u0435","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u043f\u043e\u0441\u043b\u0435"},{question:"should",variants:["\u0434\u043e\u043b\u0436\u0435\u043d","\u043f\u043e\u0442\u043e\u043c\u0443 \u0447\u0442\u043e","\u043d\u0430\u0437\u0430\u0434","\u0442\u0430\u043a\u0436\u0435","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u0434\u043e\u043b\u0436\u0435\u043d"},{question:"try",variants:["\u0434\u043e\u043b\u0436\u0435\u043d","\u043f\u043e\u0442\u043e\u043c\u0443 \u0447\u0442\u043e","\u043d\u0430\u0437\u0430\u0434","\u0442\u0430\u043a\u0436\u0435","\u043f\u044b\u0442\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f"],correct:"\u043f\u044b\u0442\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f"},{question:"in",variants:["\u043d\u0430","\u043e\u0442","\u0432","\u0441","\u0447\u0442\u043e"],correct:"\u0432"},{question:"last",variants:["\u043f\u0435\u0440\u0432\u044b\u0439","\u043f\u043e\u0442\u043e\u043c\u0443 \u0447\u0442\u043e","\u043d\u0430\u0437\u0430\u0434","\u0442\u0430\u043a\u0436\u0435","\u043f\u043e\u0441\u043b\u0435\u0434\u043d\u0438\u0439"],correct:"\u043f\u043e\u0441\u043b\u0435\u0434\u043d\u0438\u0439"},{question:"ask",variants:["\u0434\u043e\u043b\u0436\u0435\u043d","\u0441\u043f\u0440\u0430\u0448\u0438\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043d\u0430\u0437\u0430\u0434","\u0442\u0430\u043a\u0436\u0435","\u043f\u044b\u0442\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f"],correct:"\u0441\u043f\u0440\u0430\u0448\u0438\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c"},{question:"feel",variants:["\u0438\u043c\u0435\u0442\u044c","\u0436\u0435\u043b\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0447\u0443\u0432\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0445\u043e\u0442\u0435\u0442\u044c","\u0432\u0435\u0440\u043d\u0443\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u0447\u0443\u0432\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c"},{question:"when",variants:["\u043f\u0435\u0440\u0432\u044b\u0439","\u043f\u043e\u0442\u043e\u043c\u0443 \u0447\u0442\u043e","\u043f\u043e\u043a\u0430","\u0433\u0434\u0435","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"},{question:"never",variants:["\u043d\u0438\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430","\u043f\u043e\u0442\u043e\u043c\u0443 \u0447\u0442\u043e","\u043f\u043e\u043a\u0430","\u0433\u0434\u0435","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u043d\u0438\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"},{question:"become",variants:["\u043f\u0435\u0440\u0432\u044b\u0439","\u043f\u043e\u0442\u043e\u043c\u0443 \u0447\u0442\u043e","\u043f\u043e\u043a\u0430","\u0441\u0442\u0430\u043d\u043e\u0432\u0438\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u0441\u0442\u0430\u043d\u043e\u0432\u0438\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f"},{question:"between",variants:["\u043c\u0435\u0436\u0434\u0443","\u043f\u043e\u0442\u043e\u043c\u0443 \u0447\u0442\u043e","\u043f\u043e\u043a\u0430","\u0441\u0442\u0430\u043d\u043e\u0432\u0438\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u043c\u0435\u0436\u0434\u0443"},{question:"high",variants:["\u043c\u0435\u0436\u0434\u0443","\u0432\u044b\u0441\u043e\u043a\u0438\u0439","\u043f\u043e\u043a\u0430","\u0441\u0442\u0430\u043d\u043e\u0432\u0438\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u0432\u044b\u0441\u043e\u043a\u0438\u0439"},{question:"really",variants:["\u043d\u0430\u0441\u0442\u0440\u043e\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e","\u0434\u0430\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0435","\u043e\u0442\u043a\u043b\u044e\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0432\u043a\u043b\u044e\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e"},{question:"something",variants:["\u0447\u0442\u043e-\u043d\u0438\u0431\u0443\u0434\u044c","\u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e","\u0434\u0430\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0435","\u043e\u0442\u043a\u043b\u044e\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0432\u043a\u043b\u044e\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u0447\u0442\u043e-\u043d\u0438\u0431\u0443\u0434\u044c"},{question:"most",variants:["\u043c\u043e\u0440\u0435","\u0431\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0448\u0438\u043d\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e","\u043e\u0437\u0435\u0440\u043e","\u0441\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043d\u0438\u0439","\u043c\u043e\u0441\u0442"],correct:"\u0431\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0448\u0438\u043d\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e"},{question:"much",variants:["\u043c\u043e\u0440\u0435","\u043c\u043d\u043e\u0433\u043e","\u043e\u0437\u0435\u0440\u043e","\u0441\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043d\u0438\u0439","\u043c\u043e\u0441\u0442"],correct:"\u043c\u043d\u043e\u0433\u043e"},{question:"own",variants:["\u043b\u0438\u0447\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e","\u0434\u0430\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0435","\u043e\u0442\u043a\u043b\u044e\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0432\u043a\u043b\u044e\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u043b\u0438\u0447\u043d\u044b\u0439"},{question:"mean",variants:["\u0434\u043e\u043b\u0436\u0435\u043d","\u043f\u043e\u0442\u043e\u043c\u0443 \u0447\u0442\u043e","\u0437\u043d\u0430\u0447\u0438\u0442","\u0442\u0430\u043a\u0436\u0435","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u0437\u043d\u0430\u0447\u0438\u0442"},{question:"keep",variants:["\u0434\u043e\u043b\u0436\u0435\u043d","\u0445\u0440\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0437\u043d\u0430\u0447\u0438\u0442","\u0442\u0430\u043a\u0436\u0435","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u0445\u0440\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0442\u044c"},{question:"begin",variants:["\u0432\u043e\u0437\u0432\u0440\u0430\u0449\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043d\u0430\u0447\u0438\u043d\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0441\u043e\u0433\u043b\u0430\u0441\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043e\u0442\u043a\u0440\u044b\u0442\u044c","\u043f\u043e\u043b\u0443\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u043d\u0430\u0447\u0438\u043d\u0430\u0442\u044c"},{question:"every",variants:["\u0434\u0430\u0436\u0435","\u0435\u0441\u043b\u0438","\u043a\u0430\u0436\u0434\u044b\u0439","\u0433\u0434\u0435","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u043a\u0430\u0436\u0434\u044b\u0439"},{question:"same",variants:["\u043d\u0438\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430","\u043e\u0434\u0438\u043d\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0432\u044b\u0439","\u043f\u043e\u043a\u0430","\u0433\u0434\u0435","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u043e\u0434\u0438\u043d\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0432\u044b\u0439"},{question:"why",variants:["\u043f\u043e\u0447\u0435\u043c\u0443","\u043f\u043e\u0442\u043e\u043c\u0443 \u0447\u0442\u043e","\u0437\u043d\u0430\u0447\u0438\u0442","\u0442\u0430\u043a\u0436\u0435","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u043f\u043e\u0447\u0435\u043c\u0443"},{question:"seem",variants:["\u043d\u0438\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430","\u043e\u0434\u0438\u043d\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0432\u044b\u0439","\u043a\u0430\u0437\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u0433\u0434\u0435","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u043a\u0430\u0437\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f"},{question:"turn",variants:["\u0432\u043e\u0437\u0432\u0440\u0430\u0449\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043d\u0430\u0447\u0438\u043d\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0441\u043e\u0433\u043b\u0430\u0441\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043f\u043e\u0432\u043e\u0440\u0430\u0447\u0438\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043f\u043e\u043b\u0443\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u043f\u043e\u0432\u043e\u0440\u0430\u0447\u0438\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c"},{question:"hand",variants:["\u0440\u0443\u043a\u0430","\u043d\u043e\u0433\u0430","\u0433\u043e\u043b\u043e\u0432\u0430","\u0436\u0438\u0432\u043e\u0442","\u0441\u043f\u0438\u043d\u0430"],correct:"\u0440\u0443\u043a\u0430"},{question:"leg",variants:["\u0440\u0443\u043a\u0430","\u043d\u043e\u0433\u0430","\u0433\u043e\u043b\u043e\u0432\u0430","\u0436\u0438\u0432\u043e\u0442","\u0441\u043f\u0438\u043d\u0430"],correct:"\u043d\u043e\u0433\u0430"},{question:"stomach",variants:["\u0440\u0443\u043a\u0430","\u043d\u043e\u0433\u0430","\u0433\u043e\u043b\u043e\u0432\u0430","\u0436\u0438\u0432\u043e\u0442","\u0441\u043f\u0438\u043d\u0430"],correct:"\u0436\u0438\u0432\u043e\u0442"},{question:"eyes",variants:["\u0440\u0443\u043a\u0430","\u043d\u043e\u0433\u0430","\u0433\u043e\u043b\u043e\u0432\u0430","\u0433\u043b\u0430\u0437\u0430","\u0441\u043f\u0438\u043d\u0430"],correct:"\u0433\u043b\u0430\u0437\u0430"},{question:"head",variants:["\u0440\u0443\u043a\u0430","\u043d\u043e\u0433\u0430","\u0433\u043e\u043b\u043e\u0432\u0430","\u0436\u0438\u0432\u043e\u0442","\u0441\u043f\u0438\u043d\u0430"],correct:"\u0433\u043e\u043b\u043e\u0432\u0430"},{question:"again",variants:["\u043d\u0438\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430","\u043f\u043e\u0442\u043e\u043c\u0443 \u0447\u0442\u043e","\u043f\u043e\u043a\u0430","\u0441\u043d\u043e\u0432\u0430","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u0441\u043d\u043e\u0432\u0430"},{question:"place",variants:["\u043d\u0438\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430","\u043f\u043e\u0442\u043e\u043c\u0443 \u0447\u0442\u043e","\u043f\u043e\u043a\u0430","\u0441\u043d\u043e\u0432\u0430","\u043c\u0435\u0441\u0442\u043e"],correct:"\u043c\u0435\u0441\u0442\u043e"},{question:"over",variants:["\u0441\u0432\u0435\u0440\u0445","\u043f\u043e\u0442\u043e\u043c\u0443 \u0447\u0442\u043e","\u043f\u043e\u043a\u0430","\u0441\u043d\u043e\u0432\u0430","\u043c\u0435\u0441\u0442\u043e"],correct:"\u0441\u0432\u0435\u0440\u0445"},{question:"where",variants:["\u043d\u0438\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430","\u043e\u0434\u0438\u043d\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0432\u044b\u0439","\u043a\u0430\u0437\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u0433\u0434\u0435","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u0433\u0434\u0435"},{question:"question",variants:["\u043b\u0438\u0447\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e","\u0432\u043e\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0441","\u043e\u0442\u0432\u0435\u0442","\u0432\u043a\u043b\u044e\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u0432\u043e\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0441"},{question:"answer",variants:["\u043b\u0438\u0447\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e","\u0432\u043e\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0441","\u043e\u0442\u0432\u0435\u0442","\u0432\u043a\u043b\u044e\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u043e\u0442\u0432\u0435\u0442"},{question:"small",variants:["\u043b\u0435\u0433\u043a\u0438\u0439","\u043c\u0430\u043b\u0435\u043d\u044c\u043a\u0438\u0439","\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0441\u0442\u043e\u0439","\u043e\u0442\u043a\u0440\u044b\u0442\u044b\u0439","\u0437\u0430\u043a\u0440\u044b\u0442\u044b\u0439"],correct:"\u043c\u0430\u043b\u0435\u043d\u044c\u043a\u0438\u0439"},{question:"large",variants:["\u043b\u0435\u0433\u043a\u0438\u0439","\u043c\u0430\u043b\u0435\u043d\u044c\u043a\u0438\u0439","\u0431\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0448\u043e\u0439","\u043e\u0442\u043a\u0440\u044b\u0442\u044b\u0439","\u0437\u0430\u043a\u0440\u044b\u0442\u044b\u0439"],correct:"\u0431\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0448\u043e\u0439"},{question:"always",variants:["\u0434\u0430\u0436\u0435","\u0435\u0441\u043b\u0438","\u043a\u0430\u0436\u0434\u044b\u0439","\u0432\u0441\u0435\u0433\u0434\u0430","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u0432\u0441\u0435\u0433\u0434\u0430"},{question:"move",variants:["\u0434\u0432\u0438\u0433\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u043d\u0430\u0447\u0438\u043d\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0441\u043e\u0433\u043b\u0430\u0441\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043e\u0442\u043a\u0440\u044b\u0442\u044c","\u043f\u043e\u043b\u0443\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u0434\u0432\u0438\u0433\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f"},{question:"today",variants:["\u0441\u0435\u0433\u043e\u0434\u043d\u044f","\u0437\u0430\u0432\u0442\u0440\u0430","\u0432\u0447\u0435\u0440\u0430","\u0443\u0442\u0440\u043e\u043c","\u0432\u0435\u0447\u0435\u0440\u043e\u043c"],correct:"\u0441\u0435\u0433\u043e\u0434\u043d\u044f"},{question:"tomorrow",variants:["\u0441\u0435\u0433\u043e\u0434\u043d\u044f","\u0437\u0430\u0432\u0442\u0440\u0430","\u0432\u0447\u0435\u0440\u0430","\u0443\u0442\u0440\u043e\u043c","\u0432\u0435\u0447\u0435\u0440\u043e\u043c"],correct:"\u0437\u0430\u0432\u0442\u0440\u0430"},{question:"yesterday",variants:["\u0441\u0435\u0433\u043e\u0434\u043d\u044f","\u0437\u0430\u0432\u0442\u0440\u0430","\u0432\u0447\u0435\u0440\u0430","\u0443\u0442\u0440\u043e\u043c","\u0432\u0435\u0447\u0435\u0440\u043e\u043c"],correct:"\u0432\u0447\u0435\u0440\u0430"},{question:"water",variants:["\u0432\u043e\u0434\u0430","\u0435\u0434\u0430","\u0432\u043e\u0437\u0434\u0443\u0445","\u0434\u0435\u043d\u044c\u0433\u0438","\u0437\u0434\u043e\u0440\u043e\u0432\u044c\u0435"],correct:"\u0432\u043e\u0434\u0430"},{question:"money",variants:["\u0432\u043e\u0434\u0430","\u0435\u0434\u0430","\u0432\u043e\u0437\u0434\u0443\u0445","\u0434\u0435\u043d\u044c\u0433\u0438","\u0437\u0434\u043e\u0440\u043e\u0432\u044c\u0435"],correct:"\u0434\u0435\u043d\u044c\u0433\u0438"},{question:"food",variants:["\u0432\u043e\u0434\u0430","\u0435\u0434\u0430","\u0432\u043e\u0437\u0434\u0443\u0445","\u0434\u0435\u043d\u044c\u0433\u0438","\u0437\u0434\u043e\u0440\u043e\u0432\u044c\u0435"],correct:"\u0435\u0434\u0430"},{question:"air",variants:["\u0432\u043e\u0434\u0430","\u0435\u0434\u0430","\u0432\u043e\u0437\u0434\u0443\u0445","\u0434\u0435\u043d\u044c\u0433\u0438","\u0437\u0434\u043e\u0440\u043e\u0432\u044c\u0435"],correct:"\u0432\u043e\u0437\u0434\u0443\u0445"},{question:"health",variants:["\u0432\u043e\u0434\u0430","\u0435\u0434\u0430","\u0432\u043e\u0437\u0434\u0443\u0445","\u0434\u0435\u043d\u044c\u0433\u0438","\u0437\u0434\u043e\u0440\u043e\u0432\u044c\u0435"],correct:"\u0437\u0434\u043e\u0440\u043e\u0432\u044c\u0435"},{question:"young",variants:["\u043c\u043e\u043b\u043e\u0434\u043e\u0439","\u0441\u0442\u0430\u0440\u044b\u0439","\u0443\u043c\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u0437\u043b\u043e\u0439","\u0434\u043e\u0431\u0440\u044b\u0439"],correct:"\u043c\u043e\u043b\u043e\u0434\u043e\u0439"},{question:"old",variants:["\u043c\u043e\u043b\u043e\u0434\u043e\u0439","\u0441\u0442\u0430\u0440\u044b\u0439","\u0443\u043c\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u0437\u043b\u043e\u0439","\u0434\u043e\u0431\u0440\u044b\u0439"],correct:"\u0441\u0442\u0430\u0440\u044b\u0439"},{question:"clever",variants:["\u043c\u043e\u043b\u043e\u0434\u043e\u0439","\u0441\u0442\u0430\u0440\u044b\u0439","\u0443\u043c\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u0437\u043b\u043e\u0439","\u0434\u043e\u0431\u0440\u044b\u0439"],correct:"\u0443\u043c\u043d\u044b\u0439"},{question:"kind",variants:["\u043c\u043e\u043b\u043e\u0434\u043e\u0439","\u0441\u0442\u0430\u0440\u044b\u0439","\u0443\u043c\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u0437\u043b\u043e\u0439","\u0434\u043e\u0431\u0440\u044b\u0439"],correct:"\u0434\u043e\u0431\u0440\u044b\u0439"},{question:"different",variants:["\u043d\u0438\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430","\u043e\u0434\u0438\u043d\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0432\u044b\u0439","\u043a\u0430\u0437\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u0440\u0430\u0437\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u0440\u0430\u0437\u043d\u044b\u0439"},{question:"issue",variants:["\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0431\u043b\u0435\u043c\u0430","\u043e\u0434\u0438\u043d\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0432\u044b\u0439","\u043a\u0430\u0437\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u0440\u0430\u0437\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0431\u043b\u0435\u043c\u0430"},{question:"task",variants:["\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0431\u043b\u0435\u043c\u0430","\u0437\u0430\u0434\u0430\u0447\u0430","\u043a\u0430\u0437\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u0440\u0430\u0437\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u0437\u0430\u0434\u0430\u0447\u0430"},{question:"long",variants:["\u0434\u043b\u0438\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u043f\u043e\u0442\u043e\u043c\u0443 \u0447\u0442\u043e","\u043d\u0430\u0437\u0430\u0434","\u0442\u0430\u043a\u0436\u0435","\u043f\u043e\u0441\u043b\u0435\u0434\u043d\u0438\u0439"],correct:"\u0434\u043b\u0438\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0439"},{question:"short",variants:["\u0434\u043b\u0438\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u043f\u043e\u0442\u043e\u043c\u0443 \u0447\u0442\u043e","\u043a\u043e\u0440\u043e\u0442\u043a\u0438\u0439","\u0442\u0430\u043a\u0436\u0435","\u043f\u043e\u0441\u043b\u0435\u0434\u043d\u0438\u0439"],correct:"\u043a\u043e\u0440\u043e\u0442\u043a\u0438\u0439"},{question:"around",variants:["\u0434\u043b\u0438\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u043f\u043e\u0442\u043e\u043c\u0443 \u0447\u0442\u043e","\u043a\u043e\u0440\u043e\u0442\u043a\u0438\u0439","\u0432\u043e\u043a\u0440\u0443\u0433","\u043f\u043e\u0441\u043b\u0435\u0434\u043d\u0438\u0439"],correct:"\u0432\u043e\u043a\u0440\u0443\u0433"},{question:"important",variants:["\u043b\u0438\u0447\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e","\u0432\u0430\u0436\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u043e\u0442\u0432\u0435\u0442","\u0432\u043a\u043b\u044e\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u0432\u0430\u0436\u043d\u044b\u0439"},{question:"away",variants:["\u0434\u043b\u0438\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u043f\u043e\u0442\u043e\u043c\u0443 \u0447\u0442\u043e","\u043d\u0430\u0437\u0430\u0434","\u0434\u0430\u043b\u0435\u043a\u043e","\u043f\u043e\u0441\u043b\u0435\u0434\u043d\u0438\u0439"],correct:"\u0434\u0430\u043b\u0435\u043a\u043e"},{question:"hour",variants:["\u0433\u043e\u0434","\u043d\u0435\u0434\u0435\u043b\u044f","\u0432\u0440\u0435\u043c\u044f","\u0447\u0430\u0441","\u043c\u0435\u0441\u044f\u0446"],correct:"\u0447\u0430\u0441"},{question:"before",variants:["\u043d\u0438\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430","\u043e\u0434\u0438\u043d\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0432\u044b\u0439","\u043a\u0430\u0437\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u0440\u0430\u043d\u044c\u0448\u0435","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u0440\u0430\u043d\u044c\u0448\u0435"},{question:"among",variants:["\u0441\u0432\u0435\u0440\u0445","\u0441\u0440\u0435\u0434\u0438","\u043f\u043e\u043a\u0430","\u0441\u043d\u043e\u0432\u0430","\u043c\u0435\u0441\u0442\u043e"],correct:"\u0441\u0440\u0435\u0434\u0438"},{question:"lose",variants:["\u0438\u043c\u0435\u0442\u044c","\u0442\u0435\u0440\u044f\u0442\u044c","\u0431\u0440\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0445\u043e\u0442\u0435\u0442\u044c","\u0432\u0435\u0440\u043d\u0443\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u0442\u0435\u0440\u044f\u0442\u044c"},{question:"law",variants:["\u0437\u0430\u043a\u043e\u043d","\u0432\u043b\u0430\u0441\u0442\u044c","\u0441\u043f\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0435\u0434\u043b\u0438\u0432\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c","\u043d\u0430\u0440\u0443\u0448\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u043e\u0442\u0432\u0435\u0442\u0441\u0432\u0435\u043d\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u0437\u0430\u043a\u043e\u043d"},{question:"power",variants:["\u0437\u0430\u043a\u043e\u043d","\u0432\u043b\u0430\u0441\u0442\u044c","\u0441\u043f\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0435\u0434\u043b\u0438\u0432\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c","\u043d\u0430\u0440\u0443\u0448\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u043e\u0442\u0432\u0435\u0442\u0441\u0432\u0435\u043d\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u0432\u043b\u0430\u0441\u0442\u044c"},{question:"responsibility",variants:["\u0437\u0430\u043a\u043e\u043d","\u0432\u043b\u0430\u0441\u0442\u044c","\u0441\u043f\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0435\u0434\u043b\u0438\u0432\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c","\u043d\u0430\u0440\u0443\u0448\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u043e\u0442\u0432\u0435\u0442\u0441\u0432\u0435\u043d\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u043e\u0442\u0432\u0435\u0442\u0441\u0432\u0435\u043d\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c"},{question:"violation",variants:["\u0437\u0430\u043a\u043e\u043d","\u0432\u043b\u0430\u0441\u0442\u044c","\u0441\u043f\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0435\u0434\u043b\u0438\u0432\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c","\u043d\u0430\u0440\u0443\u0448\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u043e\u0442\u0432\u0435\u0442\u0441\u0432\u0435\u043d\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u043d\u0430\u0440\u0443\u0448\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435"},{question:"justice",variants:["\u0437\u0430\u043a\u043e\u043d","\u0432\u043b\u0430\u0441\u0442\u044c","\u0441\u043f\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0435\u0434\u043b\u0438\u0432\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c","\u043d\u0430\u0440\u0443\u0448\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u043e\u0442\u0432\u0435\u0442\u0441\u0432\u0435\u043d\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u0441\u043f\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0435\u0434\u043b\u0438\u0432\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c"},{question:"single",variants:["\u0430\u043a\u0442\u0438\u0432","\u043e\u0434\u0438\u043d","\u0432\u043d\u0438\u043c\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0435","\u043c\u0430\u0433\u0430\u0437\u0438\u043d"],correct:"\u043e\u0434\u0438\u043d"},{question:"second",variants:["\u0430\u043a\u0442\u0438\u0432","\u043e\u0434\u0438\u043d","\u0432\u0442\u043e\u0440\u043e\u0439","\u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0435","\u043c\u0430\u0433\u0430\u0437\u0438\u043d"],correct:"\u0432\u0442\u043e\u0440\u043e\u0439"},{question:"continue",variants:["\u043d\u0438\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430","\u043e\u0434\u0438\u043d\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0432\u044b\u0439","\u043a\u0430\u0437\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u0440\u0430\u0437\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0434\u043e\u043b\u0436\u0438\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0434\u043e\u043b\u0436\u0438\u0442\u044c"},{question:"almost",variants:["\u043f\u043e\u0447\u0442\u0438","\u043e\u0434\u0438\u043d\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0432\u044b\u0439","\u043a\u0430\u0437\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u0440\u0430\u0437\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0434\u043e\u043b\u0436\u0438\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u043f\u043e\u0447\u0442\u0438"},{question:"once",variants:["\u043f\u043e\u0447\u0442\u0438","\u043e\u0434\u0438\u043d\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0432\u044b\u0439","\u043e\u0434\u043d\u0430\u0436\u0434\u044b","\u0440\u0430\u0437\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0434\u043e\u043b\u0436\u0438\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u043e\u0434\u043d\u0430\u0436\u0434\u044b"},{question:"learn",variants:["\u043f\u043e\u0447\u0442\u0438","\u043e\u0434\u0438\u043d\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0432\u044b\u0439","\u043e\u0434\u043d\u0430\u0436\u0434\u044b","\u0443\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0434\u043e\u043b\u0436\u0438\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u0443\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044c"},{question:"several",variants:["\u0430\u043a\u0442\u0438\u0432","\u043e\u0434\u0438\u043d","\u043d\u0435\u0441\u043a\u043e\u043b\u044c\u043a\u043e","\u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0435","\u043c\u0430\u0433\u0430\u0437\u0438\u043d"],correct:"\u043d\u0435\u0441\u043a\u043e\u043b\u044c\u043a\u043e"},{question:"body",variants:["\u0430\u043a\u0442\u0438\u0432","\u043e\u0434\u0438\u043d","\u0442\u0435\u043b\u043e","\u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0435","\u043c\u0430\u0433\u0430\u0437\u0438\u043d"],correct:"\u0442\u0435\u043b\u043e"},{question:"nothing",variants:["\u0430\u043a\u0442\u0438\u0432","\u043e\u0434\u0438\u043d","\u0442\u0435\u043b\u043e","\u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0435","\u043d\u0438\u0447\u0435\u0433\u043e"],correct:"\u043d\u0438\u0447\u0435\u0433\u043e"},{question:"ago",variants:["\u0442\u043e\u043c\u0443 \u043d\u0430\u0437\u0430\u0434","\u043e\u0434\u0438\u043d","\u0442\u0435\u043b\u043e","\u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0435","\u043d\u0438\u0447\u0435\u0433\u043e"],correct:"\u0442\u043e\u043c\u0443 \u043d\u0430\u0437\u0430\u0434"},{question:"understand",variants:["\u0442\u043e\u043c\u0443 \u043d\u0430\u0437\u0430\u0434","\u043f\u043e\u043d\u0438\u043c\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0442\u0435\u043b\u043e","\u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0435","\u043d\u0438\u0447\u0435\u0433\u043e"],correct:"\u043f\u043e\u043d\u0438\u043c\u0430\u0442\u044c"},{question:"watch",variants:["\u0442\u043e\u043c\u0443 \u043d\u0430\u0437\u0430\u0434","\u043f\u043e\u043d\u0438\u043c\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0441\u043c\u043e\u0442\u0440\u0435\u0442\u044c","\u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0435","\u043d\u0438\u0447\u0435\u0433\u043e"],correct:"\u0441\u043c\u043e\u0442\u0440\u0435\u0442\u044c"},{question:"together",variants:["\u0432\u043c\u0435\u0441\u0442\u0435","\u043f\u043e\u043d\u0438\u043c\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0441\u043c\u043e\u0442\u0440\u0435\u0442\u044c","\u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0435","\u043d\u0438\u0447\u0435\u0433\u043e"],correct:"\u0432\u043c\u0435\u0441\u0442\u0435"},{question:"face",variants:["\u043b\u0438\u0447\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u043b\u0438\u0446\u043e","\u0432\u043e\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0441","\u043e\u0442\u0432\u0435\u0442","\u0432\u043a\u043b\u044e\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u043b\u0438\u0446\u043e"},{question:"mirror",variants:["\u043b\u0438\u0447\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u043b\u0438\u0446\u043e","\u0432\u043e\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0441","\u0437\u0435\u0440\u043a\u0430\u043b\u043e","\u0432\u043a\u043b\u044e\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u0437\u0435\u0440\u043a\u0430\u043b\u043e"},{question:"already",variants:["\u0443\u0436\u0435","\u043b\u0438\u0446\u043e","\u0432\u043e\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0441","\u0437\u0435\u0440\u043a\u0430\u043b\u043e","\u0432\u043a\u043b\u044e\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u0443\u0436\u0435"},{question:"read",variants:["\u0443\u0436\u0435","\u0447\u0438\u0442\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0432\u043e\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0441","\u0437\u0435\u0440\u043a\u0430\u043b\u043e","\u0432\u043a\u043b\u044e\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u0447\u0438\u0442\u0430\u0442\u044c"},{question:"allow",variants:["\u0443\u0436\u0435","\u0447\u0438\u0442\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0432\u043e\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0441","\u0437\u0435\u0440\u043a\u0430\u043b\u043e","\u0440\u0430\u0437\u0440\u0435\u0448\u0430\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u0440\u0430\u0437\u0440\u0435\u0448\u0430\u0442\u044c"},{question:"spend",variants:["\u043d\u0438\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430","\u043e\u0434\u0438\u043d\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0432\u044b\u0439","\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0432\u043e\u0434\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0440\u0430\u0437\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0432\u043e\u0434\u0438\u0442\u044c"},{question:"sure",variants:["\u043d\u0438\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430","\u043e\u0434\u0438\u043d\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0432\u044b\u0439","\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0432\u043e\u0434\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u043a\u043e\u043d\u0435\u0447\u043d\u043e","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u043a\u043e\u043d\u0435\u0447\u043d\u043e"},{question:"such",variants:["\u0442\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0439","\u043e\u0434\u0438\u043d\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0432\u044b\u0439","\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0432\u043e\u0434\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u043a\u043e\u043d\u0435\u0447\u043d\u043e","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u0442\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0439"},{question:"grow",variants:["\u0442\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0439","\u043e\u0434\u0438\u043d\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0432\u044b\u0439","\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0432\u043e\u0434\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u043a\u043e\u043d\u0435\u0447\u043d\u043e","\u0440\u0430\u0441\u0442\u0438"],correct:"\u0440\u0430\u0441\u0442\u0438"},{question:"result",variants:["\u0442\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0439","\u0440\u0435\u0437\u0443\u043b\u044c\u0442\u0430\u0442","\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0432\u043e\u0434\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u043a\u043e\u043d\u0435\u0447\u043d\u043e","\u0440\u0430\u0441\u0442\u0438"],correct:"\u0440\u0435\u0437\u0443\u043b\u044c\u0442\u0430\u0442"},{question:"reason",variants:["\u0442\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0439","\u0440\u0435\u0437\u0443\u043b\u044c\u0442\u0430\u0442","\u043f\u0440\u0438\u0447\u0438\u043d\u0430","\u043a\u043e\u043d\u0435\u0447\u043d\u043e","\u0440\u0430\u0441\u0442\u0438"],correct:"\u043f\u0440\u0438\u0447\u0438\u043d\u0430"},{question:"low",variants:["\u043c\u0435\u0436\u0434\u0443","\u0432\u044b\u0441\u043e\u043a\u0438\u0439","\u043d\u0438\u0437\u043a\u0438\u0439","\u0441\u0442\u0430\u043d\u043e\u0432\u0438\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u043d\u0438\u0437\u043a\u0438\u0439"},{question:"early",variants:["\u0442\u043e\u043c\u0443 \u043d\u0430\u0437\u0430\u0434","\u043f\u043e\u043d\u0438\u043c\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0442\u0435\u043b\u043e","\u0440\u0430\u043d\u043e","\u043d\u0438\u0447\u0435\u0433\u043e"],correct:"\u0440\u0430\u043d\u043e"},{question:"force",variants:["\u0441\u0438\u043b\u0430","\u043f\u043e\u043d\u0438\u043c\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0442\u0435\u043b\u043e","\u0440\u0430\u043d\u043e","\u043d\u0438\u0447\u0435\u0433\u043e"],correct:"\u0441\u0438\u043b\u0430"},{question:"offer",variants:["\u0441\u0438\u043b\u0430","\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043b\u043e\u0436\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u0442\u0435\u043b\u043e","\u0440\u0430\u043d\u043e","\u043d\u0438\u0447\u0435\u0433\u043e"],correct:"\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043b\u043e\u0436\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435"},{question:"enough",variants:["\u0441\u0438\u043b\u0430","\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043b\u043e\u0436\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u0434\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0430\u0442\u043e\u0447\u043d\u043e","\u0440\u0430\u043d\u043e","\u043d\u0438\u0447\u0435\u0433\u043e"],correct:"\u0434\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0430\u0442\u043e\u0447\u043d\u043e"},{question:"education",variants:["\u043e\u0431\u0440\u0430\u0437\u043e\u0432\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u0437\u0430\u0434\u0430\u0447\u0430","\u043a\u0430\u0437\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u0440\u0430\u0437\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u043e\u0431\u0440\u0430\u0437\u043e\u0432\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0435"},{question:"across",variants:["\u0447\u0435\u0440\u0435\u0437","\u043f\u043e\u0442\u043e\u043c\u0443 \u0447\u0442\u043e","\u043f\u043e\u043a\u0430","\u0441\u043d\u043e\u0432\u0430","\u043a\u043e\u0433\u0434\u0430"],correct:"\u0447\u0435\u0440\u0435\u0437"},{question:"remember",variants:["\u043f\u043e\u043c\u043d\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u043e\u0434\u0438\u043d","\u0432\u043d\u0438\u043c\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0435","\u043c\u0430\u0433\u0430\u0437\u0438\u043d"],correct:"\u043f\u043e\u043c\u043d\u0438\u0442\u044c"},{question:"maybe",variants:["\u043f\u043e\u043c\u043d\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u043e\u0434\u0438\u043d","\u0432\u043e\u0437\u043c\u043e\u0436\u043d\u043e","\u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0435","\u043c\u0430\u0433\u0430\u0437\u0438\u043d"],correct:"\u0432\u043e\u0437\u043c\u043e\u0436\u043d\u043e"},{question:"age",variants:["\u0430\u043a\u0442\u0438\u0432","\u0432\u043e\u0437\u0440\u0430\u0441\u0442","\u043d\u0435\u0441\u043a\u043e\u043b\u044c\u043a\u043e","\u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0435","\u043c\u0430\u0433\u0430\u0437\u0438\u043d"],correct:"\u0432\u043e\u0437\u0440\u0430\u0441\u0442"},{question:"including",variants:["\u0447\u0442\u043e-\u043d\u0438\u0431\u0443\u0434\u044c","\u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e","\u0434\u0430\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0435","\u0432 \u0442\u043e\u043c \u0447\u0438\u0441\u043b\u0435","\u0432\u043a\u043b\u044e\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u0432 \u0442\u043e\u043c \u0447\u0438\u0441\u043b\u0435"},{question:"consider",variants:["\u0447\u0442\u043e-\u043d\u0438\u0431\u0443\u0434\u044c","\u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e","\u0440\u0430\u0441\u0441\u043c\u0430\u0442\u0440\u0438\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0432 \u0442\u043e\u043c \u0447\u0438\u0441\u043b\u0435","\u0432\u043a\u043b\u044e\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u0440\u0430\u0441\u0441\u043c\u0430\u0442\u0440\u0438\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c"},{question:"appear",variants:["\u0447\u0442\u043e-\u043d\u0438\u0431\u0443\u0434\u044c","\u043f\u043e\u044f\u0432\u043b\u044f\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u0440\u0430\u0441\u0441\u043c\u0430\u0442\u0440\u0438\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0432 \u0442\u043e\u043c \u0447\u0438\u0441\u043b\u0435","\u0432\u043a\u043b\u044e\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u043f\u043e\u044f\u0432\u043b\u044f\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f"},{question:"actually",variants:["\u0447\u0442\u043e-\u043d\u0438\u0431\u0443\u0434\u044c","\u043f\u043e\u044f\u0432\u043b\u044f\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u0440\u0430\u0441\u0441\u043c\u0430\u0442\u0440\u0438\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0432 \u0442\u043e\u043c \u0447\u0438\u0441\u043b\u0435","\u0444\u0430\u043a\u0442\u0438\u0447\u0435\u0441\u043a\u0438"],correct:"\u0444\u0430\u043a\u0442\u0438\u0447\u0435\u0441\u043a\u0438"},{question:"probably",variants:["\u043d\u0430\u0432\u0435\u0440\u043d\u043e\u0435","\u043f\u043e\u044f\u0432\u043b\u044f\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u0440\u0430\u0441\u0441\u043c\u0430\u0442\u0440\u0438\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0432 \u0442\u043e\u043c \u0447\u0438\u0441\u043b\u0435","\u0444\u0430\u043a\u0442\u0438\u0447\u0435\u0441\u043a\u0438"],correct:"\u043d\u0430\u0432\u0435\u0440\u043d\u043e\u0435"},{question:"wait",variants:["\u0438\u043c\u0435\u0442\u044c","\u0442\u0435\u0440\u044f\u0442\u044c","\u0431\u0440\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0436\u0434\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0432\u0435\u0440\u043d\u0443\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u0436\u0434\u0430\u0442\u044c"},{question:"sense",variants:["\u0430\u043a\u0442\u0438\u0432","\u0432\u043e\u0437\u0440\u0430\u0441\u0442","\u0441\u043c\u044b\u0441\u043b","\u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0435","\u043c\u0430\u0433\u0430\u0437\u0438\u043d"],correct:"\u0441\u043c\u044b\u0441\u043b"},{question:"stay",variants:["\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u0432\u043e\u0437\u0440\u0430\u0441\u0442","\u0441\u043c\u044b\u0441\u043b","\u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0435","\u043c\u0430\u0433\u0430\u0437\u0438\u043d"],correct:"\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f"},{question:"raise",variants:["\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u0432\u043e\u0437\u0440\u0430\u0441\u0442","\u0441\u043c\u044b\u0441\u043b","\u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0435","\u043f\u043e\u0434\u043d\u0438\u043c\u0430\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u043f\u043e\u0434\u043d\u0438\u043c\u0430\u0442\u044c"},{question:"care",variants:["\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u0437\u0430\u0431\u043e\u0442\u0430","\u0441\u043c\u044b\u0441\u043b","\u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0435","\u043f\u043e\u0434\u043d\u0438\u043c\u0430\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u0437\u0430\u0431\u043e\u0442\u0430"},{question:"former",variants:["\u043e\u0441\u0442\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u0437\u0430\u0431\u043e\u0442\u0430","\u0441\u043c\u044b\u0441\u043b","\u0431\u044b\u0432\u0448\u0438\u0439","\u043f\u043e\u0434\u043d\u0438\u043c\u0430\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u0431\u044b\u0432\u0448\u0438\u0439"},{question:"sell",variants:["\u0442\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0439","\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0434\u0430\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0432\u043e\u0434\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u043a\u043e\u043d\u0435\u0447\u043d\u043e","\u0440\u0430\u0441\u0442\u0438"],correct:"\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0434\u0430\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c"},{question:"require",variants:["\u0442\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0439","\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0434\u0430\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0432\u043e\u0434\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u043a\u043e\u043d\u0435\u0447\u043d\u043e","\u0442\u0440\u0435\u0431\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0434\u0430\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c"},{question:"effort",variants:["\u0442\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0439","\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0434\u0430\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0432\u043e\u0434\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0443\u0441\u0438\u043b\u0438\u0435","\u0442\u0440\u0435\u0431\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u0443\u0441\u0438\u043b\u0438\u0435"},{question:"light",variants:["\u0441\u0432\u0435\u0442","\u0432\u0438\u0434","\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0445\u043e\u0434","\u0441\u0435\u043a\u0440\u0435\u0442","\u0442\u0438\u043f"],correct:"\u0441\u0432\u0435\u0442"},{question:"voice",variants:["\u0441\u0432\u0435\u0442","\u0433\u043e\u043b\u043e\u0441","\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0445\u043e\u0434","\u0441\u0435\u043a\u0440\u0435\u0442","\u0442\u0438\u043f"],correct:"\u0433\u043e\u043b\u043e\u0441"},{question:"whole",variants:["\u0441\u0432\u0435\u0442","\u0433\u043e\u043b\u043e\u0441","\u0432\u0435\u0441\u044c","\u0441\u0435\u043a\u0440\u0435\u0442","\u0442\u0438\u043f"],correct:"\u0432\u0435\u0441\u044c"},{question:"mind",variants:["\u0441\u0432\u0435\u0442","\u0433\u043e\u043b\u043e\u0441","\u0432\u0435\u0441\u044c","\u0440\u0430\u0437\u0443\u043c","\u0442\u0438\u043f"],correct:"\u0440\u0430\u0437\u0443\u043c"},{question:"free",variants:["\u0441\u0432\u0435\u0442","\u0433\u043e\u043b\u043e\u0441","\u0432\u0435\u0441\u044c","\u0440\u0430\u0437\u0443\u043c","\u0431\u0435\u0441\u043f\u043b\u0430\u0442\u043d\u044b\u0439"],correct:"\u0431\u0435\u0441\u043f\u043b\u0430\u0442\u043d\u044b\u0439"},{question:"price",variants:["\u0446\u0435\u043d\u0430","\u0433\u043e\u043b\u043e\u0441","\u0432\u0435\u0441\u044c","\u0440\u0430\u0437\u0443\u043c","\u0431\u0435\u0441\u043f\u043b\u0430\u0442\u043d\u044b\u0439"],correct:"\u0446\u0435\u043d\u0430"},{question:"report",variants:["\u0446\u0435\u043d\u0430","\u043e\u0442\u0447\u0435\u0442","\u0432\u0435\u0441\u044c","\u0440\u0430\u0437\u0443\u043c","\u0431\u0435\u0441\u043f\u043b\u0430\u0442\u043d\u044b\u0439"],correct:"\u043e\u0442\u0447\u0435\u0442"},{question:"less",variants:["\u0446\u0435\u043d\u0430","\u043e\u0442\u0447\u0435\u0442","\u0432\u0435\u0441\u044c","\u0440\u0430\u0437\u0443\u043c","\u043c\u0435\u043d\u044c\u0448\u0435"],correct:"\u043c\u0435\u043d\u044c\u0448\u0435"},{question:"decision",variants:["\u0446\u0435\u043d\u0430","\u043e\u0442\u0447\u0435\u0442","\u0432\u0435\u0441\u044c","\u0440\u0435\u0448\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u043c\u0435\u043d\u044c\u0448\u0435"],correct:"\u0440\u0435\u0448\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435"},{question:"hope",variants:["\u0446\u0435\u043d\u0430","\u043e\u0442\u0447\u0435\u0442","\u043d\u0430\u0434\u0435\u044f\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u0440\u0435\u0448\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u043c\u0435\u043d\u044c\u0448\u0435"],correct:"\u043d\u0430\u0434\u0435\u044f\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f"},{question:"relationship",variants:["\u0446\u0435\u043d\u0430","\u043e\u0442\u043d\u043e\u0448\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u043d\u0430\u0434\u0435\u044f\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u0440\u0435\u0448\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u043c\u0435\u043d\u044c\u0448\u0435"],correct:"\u043e\u0442\u043d\u043e\u0448\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435"},{question:"road",variants:["\u0434\u043e\u0440\u043e\u0433\u0430","\u043e\u0442\u043d\u043e\u0448\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u043d\u0430\u0434\u0435\u044f\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u0440\u0435\u0448\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u043c\u0435\u043d\u044c\u0448\u0435"],correct:"\u0434\u043e\u0440\u043e\u0433\u0430"},{question:"break",variants:["\u0434\u043e\u0440\u043e\u0433\u0430","\u043e\u0442\u043d\u043e\u0448\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u043d\u0430\u0434\u0435\u044f\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u0440\u0435\u0448\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u043f\u0435\u0440\u0435\u0440\u044b\u0432"],correct:"\u043f\u0435\u0440\u0435\u0440\u044b\u0432"},{question:"value",variants:["\u0434\u043e\u0440\u043e\u0433\u0430","\u043e\u0442\u043d\u043e\u0448\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u0437\u043d\u0430\u0447\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u0440\u0435\u0448\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u043f\u0435\u0440\u0435\u0440\u044b\u0432"],correct:"\u0437\u043d\u0430\u0447\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435"},{question:"join",variants:["\u0434\u043e\u0440\u043e\u0433\u0430","\u043e\u0442\u043d\u043e\u0448\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u0437\u043d\u0430\u0447\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u043f\u0440\u0438\u0441\u043e\u0435\u0434\u0438\u043d\u044f\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u043f\u0435\u0440\u0435\u0440\u044b\u0432"],correct:"\u043f\u0440\u0438\u0441\u043e\u0435\u0434\u0438\u043d\u044f\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f"},{question:"society",variants:["\u0434\u043e\u0440\u043e\u0433\u0430","\u043e\u0442\u043d\u043e\u0448\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u043e\u0431\u0449\u0435\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e","\u043f\u0440\u0438\u0441\u043e\u0435\u0434\u0438\u043d\u044f\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u043f\u0435\u0440\u0435\u0440\u044b\u0432"],correct:"\u043e\u0431\u0449\u0435\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e"},{question:"agree",variants:["\u0441\u043e\u0433\u043b\u0430\u0448\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u043e\u0442\u043d\u043e\u0448\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u043e\u0431\u0449\u0435\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e","\u043f\u0440\u0438\u0441\u043e\u0435\u0434\u0438\u043d\u044f\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u043f\u0435\u0440\u0435\u0440\u044b\u0432"],correct:"\u0441\u043e\u0433\u043b\u0430\u0448\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f"},{question:"especially",variants:["\u0441\u043e\u0433\u043b\u0430\u0448\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u043e\u0441\u043e\u0431\u0435\u043d\u043d\u043e","\u043e\u0431\u0449\u0435\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e","\u043f\u0440\u0438\u0441\u043e\u0435\u0434\u0438\u043d\u044f\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u043f\u0435\u0440\u0435\u0440\u044b\u0432"],correct:"\u043e\u0441\u043e\u0431\u0435\u043d\u043d\u043e"},{question:"pick",variants:["\u0441\u043e\u0433\u043b\u0430\u0448\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u043e\u0441\u043e\u0431\u0435\u043d\u043d\u043e","\u043e\u0431\u0449\u0435\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e","\u043f\u0440\u0438\u0441\u043e\u0435\u0434\u0438\u043d\u044f\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u0432\u044b\u0431\u0438\u0440\u0430\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u0432\u044b\u0431\u0438\u0440\u0430\u0442\u044c"},{question:"paper",variants:["\u0441\u043e\u0433\u043b\u0430\u0448\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u043e\u0441\u043e\u0431\u0435\u043d\u043d\u043e","\u043e\u0431\u0449\u0435\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e","\u0431\u0443\u043c\u0430\u0433\u0430","\u0432\u044b\u0431\u0438\u0440\u0430\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u0431\u0443\u043c\u0430\u0433\u0430"},{question:"space",variants:["\u0441\u043e\u0433\u043b\u0430\u0448\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u043e\u0441\u043e\u0431\u0435\u043d\u043d\u043e","\u043a\u043e\u0441\u043c\u043e\u0441","\u0431\u0443\u043c\u0430\u0433\u0430","\u0432\u044b\u0431\u0438\u0440\u0430\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u043a\u043e\u0441\u043c\u043e\u0441"},{question:"ground",variants:["\u0437\u0435\u043c\u043b\u044f","\u043e\u0441\u043e\u0431\u0435\u043d\u043d\u043e","\u043a\u043e\u0441\u043c\u043e\u0441","\u0431\u0443\u043c\u0430\u0433\u0430","\u0432\u044b\u0431\u0438\u0440\u0430\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u0437\u0435\u043c\u043b\u044f"},{question:"support",variants:["\u0437\u0435\u043c\u043b\u044f","\u043f\u043e\u0434\u0434\u0435\u0440\u0436\u043a\u0430","\u043a\u043e\u0441\u043c\u043e\u0441","\u0431\u0443\u043c\u0430\u0433\u0430","\u0432\u044b\u0431\u0438\u0440\u0430\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u043f\u043e\u0434\u0434\u0435\u0440\u0436\u043a\u0430"},{question:"event",variants:["\u0437\u0435\u043c\u043b\u044f","\u043f\u043e\u0434\u0434\u0435\u0440\u0436\u043a\u0430","\u043a\u043e\u0441\u043c\u043e\u0441","\u0431\u0443\u043c\u0430\u0433\u0430","\u0441\u043e\u0431\u044b\u0442\u0438\u0435"],correct:"\u0441\u043e\u0431\u044b\u0442\u0438\u0435"},{question:"couple",variants:["\u0437\u0435\u043c\u043b\u044f","\u043f\u043e\u0434\u0434\u0435\u0440\u0436\u043a\u0430","\u043a\u043e\u0441\u043c\u043e\u0441","\u043f\u0430\u0440\u0430","\u0441\u043e\u0431\u044b\u0442\u0438\u0435"],correct:"\u043f\u0430\u0440\u0430"},{question:"base",variants:["\u0437\u0435\u043c\u043b\u044f","\u043f\u043e\u0434\u0434\u0435\u0440\u0436\u043a\u0430","\u043e\u0441\u043d\u043e\u0432\u0430","\u043f\u0430\u0440\u0430","\u0441\u043e\u0431\u044b\u0442\u0438\u0435"],correct:"\u043e\u0441\u043d\u043e\u0432\u0430"},{question:"need",variants:["\u0432\u043e\u0437\u0432\u0440\u0430\u0449\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0431\u0440\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043d\u0443\u0436\u043d\u043e","\u043e\u0442\u043a\u0440\u044b\u0442\u044c","\u043f\u043e\u043b\u0443\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u043d\u0443\u0436\u043d\u043e"},{question:"eat",variants:["\u0435\u0441\u0442\u044c","\u0431\u0440\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043d\u0443\u0436\u043d\u043e","\u043e\u0442\u043a\u0440\u044b\u0442\u044c","\u043f\u043e\u043b\u0443\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u0435\u0441\u0442\u044c"},{question:"half",variants:["\u0435\u0441\u0442\u044c","\u043f\u043e\u043b\u043e\u0432\u0438\u043d\u0430","\u043d\u0443\u0436\u043d\u043e","\u043e\u0442\u043a\u0440\u044b\u0442\u044c","\u043f\u043e\u043b\u0443\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u043f\u043e\u043b\u043e\u0432\u0438\u043d\u0430"},{question:"cost",variants:["\u0435\u0441\u0442\u044c","\u043f\u043e\u043b\u043e\u0432\u0438\u043d\u0430","\u043d\u0443\u0436\u043d\u043e","\u0441\u0442\u043e\u0438\u043c\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c","\u043f\u043e\u043b\u0443\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044c"],correct:"\u0441\u0442\u043e\u0438\u043c\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c"},{question:"cover",variants:["\u0435\u0441\u0442\u044c","\u043f\u043e\u043b\u043e\u0432\u0438\u043d\u0430","\u043d\u0443\u0436\u043d\u043e","\u0441\u0442\u043e\u0438\u043c\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c","\u043f\u043e\u043a\u0440\u044b\u0442\u0438\u0435"],correct:"\u043f\u043e\u043a\u0440\u044b\u0442\u0438\u0435"},{question:"quite",variants:["\u0434\u043e\u0432\u043e\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e","\u043f\u043e\u043b\u043e\u0432\u0438\u043d\u0430","\u043d\u0443\u0436\u043d\u043e","\u0441\u0442\u043e\u0438\u043c\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c","\u043f\u043e\u043a\u0440\u044b\u0442\u0438\u0435"],correct:"\u0434\u043e\u0432\u043e\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e"},{question:"clear",variants:["\u0434\u043e\u0432\u043e\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e","\u043f\u043e\u043b\u043e\u0432\u0438\u043d\u0430","\u0447\u0438\u0441\u0442\u043e","\u0441\u0442\u043e\u0438\u043c\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c","\u043f\u043e\u043a\u0440\u044b\u0442\u0438\u0435"],correct:"\u0447\u0438\u0441\u0442\u043e"},{question:"recent",variants:["\u0434\u043e\u0432\u043e\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e","\u043f\u043e\u043b\u043e\u0432\u0438\u043d\u0430","\u0447\u0438\u0441\u0442\u043e","\u043d\u0435\u0434\u0430\u0432\u043d\u0438\u0439","\u043f\u043e\u043a\u0440\u044b\u0442\u0438\u0435"],correct:"\u043d\u0435\u0434\u0430\u0432\u043d\u0438\u0439"},{question:"describe",variants:["\u0434\u043e\u0432\u043e\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e","\u043e\u043f\u0438\u0441\u044b\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0447\u0438\u0441\u0442\u043e","\u043d\u0435\u0434\u0430\u0432\u043d\u0438\u0439","\u043f\u043e\u043a\u0440\u044b\u0442\u0438\u0435"],correct:"\u043e\u043f\u0438\u0441\u044b\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c"},{question:"wall",variants:["\u0441\u0442\u0435\u043d\u0430","\u043e\u043f\u0438\u0441\u044b\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0447\u0438\u0441\u0442\u043e","\u043d\u0435\u0434\u0430\u0432\u043d\u0438\u0439","\u043f\u043e\u043a\u0440\u044b\u0442\u0438\u0435"],correct:"\u0441\u0442\u0435\u043d\u0430"},{question:"movie",variants:["\u0441\u0442\u0435\u043d\u0430","\u043e\u043f\u0438\u0441\u044b\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0447\u0438\u0441\u0442\u043e","\u043d\u0435\u0434\u0430\u0432\u043d\u0438\u0439","\u043f\u043e\u043a\u0440\u044b\u0442\u0438\u0435"],correct:"\u043a\u0438\u043d\u043e"},{question:"certain",variants:["\u0441\u0442\u0435\u043d\u0430","\u043e\u043f\u0438\u0441\u044b\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043e\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u0435\u043b\u0435\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u043d\u0435\u0434\u0430\u0432\u043d\u0438\u0439","\u043f\u043e\u043a\u0440\u044b\u0442\u0438\u0435"],correct:"\u043e\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u0435\u043b\u0435\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0439"},{question:"north",variants:["\u0441\u0442\u0435\u043d\u0430","\u043e\u043f\u0438\u0441\u044b\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043e\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u0435\u043b\u0435\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u043d\u0435\u0434\u0430\u0432\u043d\u0438\u0439","\u0441\u0435\u0432\u0435\u0440"],correct:"\u0441\u0435\u0432\u0435\u0440"},{question:"third",variants:["\u0441\u0442\u0435\u043d\u0430","\u043e\u043f\u0438\u0441\u044b\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043e\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u0435\u043b\u0435\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u0442\u0440\u0435\u0442\u0438\u0439","\u0441\u0435\u0432\u0435\u0440"],correct:"\u0442\u0440\u0435\u0442\u0438\u0439"},{question:"catch",variants:["\u0441\u0442\u0435\u043d\u0430","\u043b\u043e\u0432\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u043e\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u0435\u043b\u0435\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u0442\u0440\u0435\u0442\u0438\u0439","\u0441\u0435\u0432\u0435\u0440"],correct:"\u043b\u043e\u0432\u0438\u0442\u044c"},{question:"step",variants:["\u0441\u0442\u0435\u043d\u0430","\u0448\u0430\u0433","\u043e\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u0435\u043b\u0435\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u0442\u0440\u0435\u0442\u0438\u0439","\u0441\u0435\u0432\u0435\u0440"],correct:"\u0448\u0430\u0433"},{question:"attention",variants:["\u0430\u043a\u0442\u0438\u0432","\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043c\u0435\u0442","\u0432\u043d\u0438\u043c\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0435","\u0441\u043e\u0441\u0442\u043e\u044f\u043d\u0438\u0435"],correct:"\u0432\u043d\u0438\u043c\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0435"},{question:"draw",variants:["\u0440\u0438\u0441\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043c\u0435\u0442","\u0432\u043d\u0438\u043c\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0435","\u0441\u043e\u0441\u0442\u043e\u044f\u043d\u0438\u0435"],correct:"\u0440\u0438\u0441\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c"},{question:"tree",variants:["\u0440\u0438\u0441\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0434\u0435\u0440\u0435\u0432\u043e","\u0432\u043d\u0438\u043c\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0435","\u0441\u043e\u0441\u0442\u043e\u044f\u043d\u0438\u0435"],correct:"\u0434\u0435\u0440\u0435\u0432\u043e"},{question:"nearly",variants:["\u0440\u0438\u0441\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0434\u0435\u0440\u0435\u0432\u043e","\u0432\u043d\u0438\u043c\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0435","\u043e\u043a\u043e\u043b\u043e"],correct:"\u043e\u043a\u043e\u043b\u043e"},{question:"choose",variants:["\u0440\u0438\u0441\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0434\u0435\u0440\u0435\u0432\u043e","\u0432\u044b\u0431\u0435\u0440\u0438\u0442\u0435","\u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0435","\u043e\u043a\u043e\u043b\u043e"],correct:"\u0432\u044b\u0431\u0435\u0440\u0438\u0442\u0435"},{question:"hair",variants:["\u0440\u0438\u0441\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0434\u0435\u0440\u0435\u0432\u043e","\u0432\u044b\u0431\u0435\u0440\u0438\u0442\u0435","\u0432\u043e\u043b\u043e\u0441\u044b","\u043e\u043a\u043e\u043b\u043e"],correct:"\u0432\u043e\u043b\u043e\u0441\u044b"},{question:"point",variants:["\u0442\u043e\u0447\u043a\u0430","\u0434\u0435\u0440\u0435\u0432\u043e","\u0432\u044b\u0431\u0435\u0440\u0438\u0442\u0435","\u0432\u043e\u043b\u043e\u0441\u044b","\u043e\u043a\u043e\u043b\u043e"],correct:"\u0442\u043e\u0447\u043a\u0430"},{question:"century",variants:["\u0442\u043e\u0447\u043a\u0430","\u0432\u0435\u043a","\u0432\u044b\u0431\u0435\u0440\u0438\u0442\u0435","\u0432\u043e\u043b\u043e\u0441\u044b","\u043e\u043a\u043e\u043b\u043e"],correct:"\u0432\u0435\u043a"},{question:"evidence",variants:["\u0442\u043e\u0447\u043a\u0430","\u0432\u0435\u043a","\u0441\u0432\u0438\u0434\u0435\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e","\u0432\u043e\u043b\u043e\u0441\u044b","\u043e\u043a\u043e\u043b\u043e"],correct:"\u0441\u0432\u0438\u0434\u0435\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e"},{question:"soon",variants:["\u0442\u043e\u0447\u043a\u0430","\u0432\u0435\u043a","\u0441\u0432\u0438\u0434\u0435\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e","\u0432\u043e\u043b\u043e\u0441\u044b","\u0441\u043a\u043e\u0440\u043e"],correct:"\u0441\u043a\u043e\u0440\u043e"},{question:"chance",variants:["\u0448\u0430\u043d\u0441","\u0432\u0435\u043a","\u0441\u0432\u0438\u0434\u0435\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e","\u0432\u043e\u043b\u043e\u0441\u044b","\u0441\u043a\u043e\u0440\u043e"],correct:"\u0448\u0430\u043d\u0441"},{question:"energy",variants:["\u0448\u0430\u043d\u0441","\u0432\u0435\u043a","\u0441\u0432\u0438\u0434\u0435\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e","\u044d\u043d\u0435\u0440\u0433\u0438\u044f","\u0441\u043a\u043e\u0440\u043e"],correct:"\u044d\u043d\u0435\u0440\u0433\u0438\u044f"},{question:"summer",variants:["\u0448\u0430\u043d\u0441","\u043b\u0435\u0442\u043e","\u0441\u0432\u0438\u0434\u0435\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e","\u044d\u043d\u0435\u0440\u0433\u0438\u044f","\u0441\u043a\u043e\u0440\u043e"],correct:"\u043b\u0435\u0442\u043e"},{question:"available",variants:["\u0448\u0430\u043d\u0441","\u043b\u0435\u0442\u043e","\u0438\u043c\u0435\u0435\u0442\u0441\u044f \u0432 \u043d\u0430\u043b\u0438\u0447\u0438\u0438","\u044d\u043d\u0435\u0440\u0433\u0438\u044f","\u0441\u043a\u043e\u0440\u043e"],correct:"\u0438\u043c\u0435\u0435\u0442\u0441\u044f \u0432 \u043d\u0430\u043b\u0438\u0447\u0438\u0438"},{question:"plant",variants:["\u0440\u0430\u0441\u0442\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u043b\u0435\u0442\u043e","\u0438\u043c\u0435\u0435\u0442\u0441\u044f \u0432 \u043d\u0430\u043b\u0438\u0447\u0438\u0438","\u044d\u043d\u0435\u0440\u0433\u0438\u044f","\u0441\u043a\u043e\u0440\u043e"],correct:"\u0440\u0430\u0441\u0442\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435"},{question:"opportunity",variants:["\u0440\u0430\u0441\u0442\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u043b\u0435\u0442\u043e","\u0438\u043c\u0435\u0435\u0442\u0441\u044f \u0432 \u043d\u0430\u043b\u0438\u0447\u0438\u0438","\u0432\u043e\u0437\u043c\u043e\u0436\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c","\u0441\u043a\u043e\u0440\u043e"],correct:"\u0432\u043e\u0437\u043c\u043e\u0436\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c"},{question:"term",variants:["\u0440\u0430\u0441\u0442\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u043b\u0435\u0442\u043e","\u0438\u043c\u0435\u0435\u0442\u0441\u044f \u0432 \u043d\u0430\u043b\u0438\u0447\u0438\u0438","\u0432\u043e\u0437\u043c\u043e\u0436\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c","\u0441\u0440\u043e\u043a"],correct:"\u0441\u0440\u043e\u043a"},{question:"choice",variants:["\u0440\u0430\u0441\u0442\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u0432\u044b\u0431\u043e\u0440","\u0438\u043c\u0435\u0435\u0442\u0441\u044f \u0432 \u043d\u0430\u043b\u0438\u0447\u0438\u0438","\u0432\u043e\u0437\u043c\u043e\u0436\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c","\u0441\u0440\u043e\u043a"],correct:"\u0432\u044b\u0431\u043e\u0440"},{question:"rule",variants:["\u0440\u0430\u0441\u0442\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u0432\u044b\u0431\u043e\u0440","\u043f\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u043b\u043e","\u0432\u043e\u0437\u043c\u043e\u0436\u043d\u043e\u0441\u0442\u044c","\u0441\u0440\u043e\u043a"],correct:"\u043f\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u043b\u043e"},{question:"south",variants:["\u0440\u0430\u0441\u0442\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u0432\u044b\u0431\u043e\u0440","\u043f\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u043b\u043e","\u044e\u0433","\u0441\u0440\u043e\u043a"],correct:"\u044e\u0433"},{question:"husband",variants:["\u043c\u0443\u0436","\u0432\u044b\u0431\u043e\u0440","\u043f\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u043b\u043e","\u044e\u0433","\u0441\u0440\u043e\u043a"],correct:"\u043c\u0443\u0436"},{question:"wife",variants:["\u043c\u0443\u0436","\u0436\u0435\u043d\u0430","\u043f\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u043b\u043e","\u044e\u0433","\u0441\u0440\u043e\u043a"],correct:"\u0436\u0435\u043d\u0430"},{question:"population",variants:["\u043c\u0443\u0436","\u0436\u0435\u043d\u0430","\u043f\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u043b\u043e","\u044e\u0433","\u043d\u0430\u0441\u0435\u043b\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435"],correct:"\u043d\u0430\u0441\u0435\u043b\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435"},{question:"current",variants:["\u043c\u0443\u0436","\u0436\u0435\u043d\u0430","\u0442\u0435\u043a\u0443\u0449\u0438\u0439","\u044e\u0433","\u043d\u0430\u0441\u0435\u043b\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435"],correct:"\u0442\u0435\u043a\u0443\u0449\u0438\u0439"},{question:"fire",variants:["\u043c\u0443\u0436","\u0436\u0435\u043d\u0430","\u0442\u0435\u043a\u0443\u0449\u0438\u0439","\u043e\u0433\u043e\u043d\u044c","\u043d\u0430\u0441\u0435\u043b\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435"],correct:"\u043e\u0433\u043e\u043d\u044c"},{question:"future",variants:["\u0431\u0443\u0434\u0443\u0449\u0435\u0435","\u0436\u0435\u043d\u0430","\u0442\u0435\u043a\u0443\u0449\u0438\u0439","\u043e\u0433\u043e\u043d\u044c","\u043d\u0430\u0441\u0435\u043b\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435"],correct:"\u0431\u0443\u0434\u0443\u0449\u0435\u0435"},{question:"wrong",variants:["\u0431\u0443\u0434\u0443\u0449\u0435\u0435","\u043d\u0435\u043f\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u043b\u044c\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u0442\u0435\u043a\u0443\u0449\u0438\u0439","\u043e\u0433\u043e\u043d\u044c","\u043d\u0430\u0441\u0435\u043b\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435"],correct:"\u043d\u0435\u043f\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u043b\u044c\u043d\u044b\u0439"},{question:"defense",variants:["\u0431\u0443\u0434\u0443\u0449\u0435\u0435","\u043d\u0435\u043f\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u043b\u044c\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u0442\u0435\u043a\u0443\u0449\u0438\u0439","\u043e\u0433\u043e\u043d\u044c","\u0437\u0430\u0449\u0438\u0442\u0430"],correct:"\u0437\u0430\u0449\u0438\u0442\u0430"},{question:"myself",variants:["\u0431\u0443\u0434\u0443\u0449\u0435\u0435","\u043d\u0435\u043f\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u043b\u044c\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u0441\u0430\u043c","\u043e\u0433\u043e\u043d\u044c","\u0437\u0430\u0449\u0438\u0442\u0430"],correct:"\u0441\u0430\u043c"},{question:"west",variants:["\u0431\u0443\u0434\u0443\u0449\u0435\u0435","\u043d\u0435\u043f\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u043b\u044c\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u0441\u0430\u043c","\u0437\u0430\u043f\u0430\u0434","\u0437\u0430\u0449\u0438\u0442\u0430"],correct:"\u0437\u0430\u043f\u0430\u0434"},{question:"subject",variants:["\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043c\u0435\u0442","\u043d\u0435\u043f\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u043b\u044c\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u0441\u0430\u043c","\u0437\u0430\u043f\u0430\u0434","\u0437\u0430\u0449\u0438\u0442\u0430"],correct:"\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043c\u0435\u0442"},{question:"rest",variants:["\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043c\u0435\u0442","\u043e\u0442\u0434\u044b\u0445","\u0441\u0430\u043c","\u0437\u0430\u043f\u0430\u0434","\u0437\u0430\u0449\u0438\u0442\u0430"],correct:"\u043e\u0442\u0434\u044b\u0445"},{question:"behaviour",variants:["\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043c\u0435\u0442","\u043e\u0442\u0434\u044b\u0445","\u043f\u043e\u0432\u0435\u0434\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u0437\u0430\u043f\u0430\u0434","\u0437\u0430\u0449\u0438\u0442\u0430"],correct:"\u043f\u043e\u0432\u0435\u0434\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435"},{question:"performance",variants:["\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043c\u0435\u0442","\u043e\u0442\u0434\u044b\u0445","\u0441\u0430\u043c","\u0437\u0430\u043f\u0430\u0434","\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u0441\u0442\u0430\u0432\u043b\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435"],correct:"\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u0441\u0442\u0430\u0432\u043b\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435"},{question:"fight",variants:["\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043c\u0435\u0442","\u043e\u0442\u0434\u044b\u0445","\u0441\u0440\u0430\u0436\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u0437\u0430\u043f\u0430\u0434","\u0437\u0430\u0449\u0438\u0442\u0430"],correct:"\u0441\u0440\u0430\u0436\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f"},{question:"top",variants:["\u0432\u0435\u0440\u0448\u0438\u043d\u0430","\u043e\u0442\u0434\u044b\u0445","\u0441\u0440\u0430\u0436\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u0437\u0430\u043f\u0430\u0434","\u0437\u0430\u0449\u0438\u0442\u0430"],correct:"\u0432\u0435\u0440\u0448\u0438\u043d\u0430"},{question:"quickly",variants:["\u0431\u044b\u0441\u0442\u0440\u043e","\u043e\u0442\u0434\u044b\u0445","\u0441\u0440\u0430\u0436\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u0437\u0430\u043f\u0430\u0434","\u0437\u0430\u0449\u0438\u0442\u0430"],correct:"\u0431\u044b\u0441\u0442\u0440\u043e"},{question:"bed",variants:["\u043a\u0440\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043e\u0442\u0434\u044b\u0445","\u0441\u0440\u0430\u0436\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u0437\u0430\u043f\u0430\u0434","\u0437\u0430\u0449\u0438\u0442\u0430"],correct:"\u043a\u0440\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c"},{question:"blood",variants:["\u043a\u0440\u043e\u0432\u044c","\u043e\u0442\u0434\u044b\u0445","\u0441\u0440\u0430\u0436\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u0437\u0430\u043f\u0430\u0434","\u0437\u0430\u0449\u0438\u0442\u0430"],correct:"\u043a\u0440\u043e\u0432\u044c"},{question:"fine",variants:["\u043a\u0440\u043e\u0432\u044c","\u043e\u0442\u0434\u044b\u0445","\u0441\u0440\u0430\u0436\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u043e\u0442\u043b\u0438\u0447\u043d\u043e","\u0437\u0430\u0449\u0438\u0442\u0430"],correct:"\u043e\u0442\u043b\u0438\u0447\u043d\u043e"},{question:"enter",variants:["\u043a\u0440\u043e\u0432\u044c","\u0432\u0445\u043e\u0434\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0441\u0440\u0430\u0436\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u043e\u0442\u043b\u0438\u0447\u043d\u043e","\u0437\u0430\u0449\u0438\u0442\u0430"],correct:"\u0432\u0445\u043e\u0434\u0438\u0442\u044c"},{question:"share",variants:["\u043f\u043e\u0434\u0435\u043b\u0438\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u0432\u0445\u043e\u0434\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0441\u0440\u0430\u0436\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u043e\u0442\u043b\u0438\u0447\u043d\u043e","\u0437\u0430\u0449\u0438\u0442\u0430"],correct:"\u043f\u043e\u0434\u0435\u043b\u0438\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f"},{question:"hot",variants:["\u043f\u043e\u0434\u0435\u043b\u0438\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u0432\u0445\u043e\u0434\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0433\u043e\u0440\u044f\u0447\u0438\u0439","\u043e\u0442\u043b\u0438\u0447\u043d\u043e","\u0437\u0430\u0449\u0438\u0442\u0430"],correct:"\u0433\u043e\u0440\u044f\u0447\u0438\u0439"},{question:"response",variants:["\u043f\u043e\u0434\u0435\u043b\u0438\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u0432\u0445\u043e\u0434\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0433\u043e\u0440\u044f\u0447\u0438\u0439","\u043e\u0442\u043b\u0438\u0447\u043d\u043e","\u043e\u0442\u043a\u043b\u0438\u043a"],correct:"\u043e\u0442\u043a\u043b\u0438\u043a"},{question:"east",variants:["\u043f\u043e\u0434\u0435\u043b\u0438\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u0432\u043e\u0441\u0442\u043e\u043a","\u0433\u043e\u0440\u044f\u0447\u0438\u0439","\u043e\u0442\u043b\u0438\u0447\u043d\u043e","\u043e\u0442\u043a\u043b\u0438\u043a"],correct:"\u0432\u043e\u0441\u0442\u043e\u043a"},{question:"size",variants:["\u043f\u043e\u0434\u0435\u043b\u0438\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u0432\u043e\u0441\u0442\u043e\u043a","\u0433\u043e\u0440\u044f\u0447\u0438\u0439","\u0440\u0430\u0437\u043c\u0435\u0440","\u043e\u0442\u043a\u043b\u0438\u043a"],correct:"\u0440\u0430\u0437\u043c\u0435\u0440"},{question:"ready",variants:["\u0433\u043e\u0442\u043e\u0432","\u0432\u043e\u0441\u0442\u043e\u043a","\u0433\u043e\u0440\u044f\u0447\u0438\u0439","\u0440\u0430\u0437\u043c\u0435\u0440","\u043e\u0442\u043a\u043b\u0438\u043a"],correct:"\u0433\u043e\u0442\u043e\u0432"},{question:"simple",variants:["\u0433\u043e\u0442\u043e\u0432","\u0432\u043e\u0441\u0442\u043e\u043a","\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0441\u0442\u043e\u0439","\u0440\u0430\u0437\u043c\u0435\u0440","\u043e\u0442\u043a\u043b\u0438\u043a"],correct:"\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0441\u0442\u043e\u0439"},{question:"quality",variants:["\u0433\u043e\u0442\u043e\u0432","\u0432\u043e\u0441\u0442\u043e\u043a","\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0441\u0442\u043e\u0439","\u0440\u0430\u0437\u043c\u0435\u0440","\u043a\u0430\u0447\u0435\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e"],correct:"\u043a\u0430\u0447\u0435\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e"},{question:"pressure",variants:["\u0433\u043e\u0442\u043e\u0432","\u0434\u0430\u0432\u043b\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0441\u0442\u043e\u0439","\u0440\u0430\u0437\u043c\u0435\u0440","\u043a\u0430\u0447\u0435\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e"],correct:"\u0434\u0430\u0432\u043b\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435"},{question:"amount",variants:["\u0433\u043e\u0442\u043e\u0432","\u0434\u0430\u0432\u043b\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0441\u0442\u043e\u0439","\u0441\u0443\u043c\u043c\u0430","\u043a\u0430\u0447\u0435\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e"],correct:"\u0441\u0443\u043c\u043c\u0430"},{question:"trade",variants:["\u0442\u043e\u0440\u0433\u043e\u0432\u043b\u044f","\u0434\u0430\u0432\u043b\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435","\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0441\u0442\u043e\u0439","\u0441\u0443\u043c\u043c\u0430","\u043a\u0430\u0447\u0435\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e"],correct:"\u0442\u043e\u0440\u0433\u043e\u0432\u043b\u044f"},{question:"election",variants:["\u0442\u043e\u0440\u0433\u043e\u0432\u043b\u044f","\u0432\u044b\u0431\u043e\u0440\u044b","\u043f\u0440\u043e\u0441\u0442\u043e\u0439","\u0441\u0443\u043c\u043c\u0430","\u043a\u0430\u0447\u0435\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e"],correct:"\u0432\u044b\u0431\u043e\u0440\u044b"},{question:"skill",variants:["\u0442\u043e\u0440\u0433\u043e\u0432\u043b\u044f","\u0432\u044b\u0431\u043e\u0440\u044b","\u043d\u0430\u0432\u044b\u043a","\u0441\u0443\u043c\u043c\u0430","\u043a\u0430\u0447\u0435\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e"],correct:"\u043d\u0430\u0432\u044b\u043a"},{question:"compare",variants:["\u0441\u0440\u0430\u0432\u043d\u0438\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0432\u044b\u0431\u043e\u0440\u044b","\u043d\u0430\u0432\u044b\u043a","\u0441\u0443\u043c\u043c\u0430","\u043a\u0430\u0447\u0435\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e"],correct:"\u0441\u0440\u0430\u0432\u043d\u0438\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c"},{question:"miss",variants:["\u0441\u0440\u0430\u0432\u043d\u0438\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0432\u044b\u0431\u043e\u0440\u044b","\u043d\u0430\u0432\u044b\u043a","\u0441\u043a\u0443\u0447\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043a\u0430\u0447\u0435\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e"],correct:"\u0441\u043a\u0443\u0447\u0430\u0442\u044c"},{question:"indeed",variants:["\u0441\u0440\u0430\u0432\u043d\u0438\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0432\u044b\u0431\u043e\u0440\u044b","\u043d\u0430\u0432\u044b\u043a","\u0441\u043a\u0443\u0447\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e"],correct:"\u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e"},{question:"example",variants:["\u0441\u0440\u0430\u0432\u043d\u0438\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043f\u0440\u0438\u043c\u0435\u0440","\u043d\u0430\u0432\u044b\u043a","\u0441\u043a\u0443\u0447\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e"],correct:"\u043f\u0440\u0438\u043c\u0435\u0440"},{question:"dark",variants:["\u0442\u0435\u043c\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u043f\u0440\u0438\u043c\u0435\u0440","\u043d\u0430\u0432\u044b\u043a","\u0441\u043a\u0443\u0447\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e"],correct:"\u0442\u0435\u043c\u043d\u044b\u0439"},{question:"public",variants:["\u0442\u0435\u043c\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u043f\u0440\u0438\u043c\u0435\u0440","\u043e\u0431\u0449\u0435\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0435\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u0441\u043a\u0443\u0447\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e"],correct:"\u043e\u0431\u0449\u0435\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0435\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0439"},{question:"rather",variants:["\u0442\u0435\u043c\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u043f\u0440\u0438\u043c\u0435\u0440","\u043e\u0431\u0449\u0435\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0435\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u0441\u043a\u043e\u0440\u0435\u0435","\u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e"],correct:"\u0441\u043a\u043e\u0440\u0435\u0435"},{question:"guess",variants:["\u0442\u0435\u043c\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u0443\u0433\u0430\u0434\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043e\u0431\u0449\u0435\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0435\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u0441\u043a\u043e\u0440\u0435\u0435","\u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e"],correct:"\u0443\u0433\u0430\u0434\u0430\u0442\u044c"},{question:"forget",variants:["\u0437\u0430\u0431\u044b\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0443\u0433\u0430\u0434\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043e\u0431\u0449\u0435\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0435\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u0441\u043a\u043e\u0440\u0435\u0435","\u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e"],correct:"\u0437\u0430\u0431\u044b\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c"},{question:"remove",variants:["\u0437\u0430\u0431\u044b\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0443\u0433\u0430\u0434\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0443\u0434\u0430\u043b\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0441\u043a\u043e\u0440\u0435\u0435","\u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e"],correct:"\u0443\u0434\u0430\u043b\u0438\u0442\u044c"},{question:"cold",variants:["\u0437\u0430\u0431\u044b\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0443\u0433\u0430\u0434\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0443\u0434\u0430\u043b\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0445\u043e\u043b\u043e\u0434\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u0434\u0435\u0439\u0441\u0442\u0432\u0438\u0442\u0435\u043b\u044c\u043d\u043e"],correct:"\u0445\u043e\u043b\u043e\u0434\u043d\u044b\u0439"},{question:"main",variants:["\u0437\u0430\u0431\u044b\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0443\u0433\u0430\u0434\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0443\u0434\u0430\u043b\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0445\u043e\u043b\u043e\u0434\u043d\u044b\u0439","\u043e\u0441\u043d\u043e\u0432\u043d\u043e\u0439"],correct:"\u043e\u0441\u043d\u043e\u0432\u043d\u043e\u0439"},{question:"memory",variants:["\u0437\u0430\u0431\u044b\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0443\u0433\u0430\u0434\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0443\u0434\u0430\u043b\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u043f\u0430\u043c\u044f\u0442\u044c","\u043e\u0441\u043d\u043e\u0432\u043d\u043e\u0439"],correct:"\u043f\u0430\u043c\u044f\u0442\u044c"},{question:"spring",variants:["\u0437\u0430\u0431\u044b\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0432\u0435\u0441\u043d\u0430","\u0443\u0434\u0430\u043b\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u043f\u0430\u043c\u044f\u0442\u044c","\u043e\u0441\u043d\u043e\u0432\u043d\u043e\u0439"],correct:"\u0432\u0435\u0441\u043d\u0430"},{question:"imagine",variants:["\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u0441\u0442\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0432\u0435\u0441\u043d\u0430","\u0443\u0434\u0430\u043b\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u043f\u0430\u043c\u044f\u0442\u044c","\u043e\u0441\u043d\u043e\u0432\u043d\u043e\u0439"],correct:"\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u0441\u0442\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0442\u044c"},{question:"tonight",variants:["\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u0441\u0442\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0432\u0435\u0441\u043d\u0430","\u0441\u0435\u0433\u043e\u0434\u043d\u044f \u043d\u043e\u0447\u044c\u044e","\u043f\u0430\u043c\u044f\u0442\u044c","\u043e\u0441\u043d\u043e\u0432\u043d\u043e\u0439"],correct:"\u0441\u0435\u0433\u043e\u0434\u043d\u044f \u043d\u043e\u0447\u044c\u044e"},{question:"impact",variants:["\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u0441\u0442\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0432\u0435\u0441\u043d\u0430","\u0441\u0435\u0433\u043e\u0434\u043d\u044f \u043d\u043e\u0447\u044c\u044e","\u043f\u0430\u043c\u044f\u0442\u044c","\u0432\u043b\u0438\u044f\u043d\u0438\u0435"],correct:"\u0432\u043b\u0438\u044f\u043d\u0438\u0435"},{question:"charge",variants:["\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u0441\u0442\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0437\u0430\u0440\u044f\u0436\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0441\u0435\u0433\u043e\u0434\u043d\u044f \u043d\u043e\u0447\u044c\u044e","\u043f\u0430\u043c\u044f\u0442\u044c","\u0432\u043b\u0438\u044f\u043d\u0438\u0435"],correct:"\u0437\u0430\u0440\u044f\u0436\u0430\u0442\u044c"},{question:"peace",variants:["\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u0441\u0442\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0437\u0430\u0440\u044f\u0436\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0441\u0435\u0433\u043e\u0434\u043d\u044f \u043d\u043e\u0447\u044c\u044e","\u043c\u0438\u0440","\u0432\u043b\u0438\u044f\u043d\u0438\u0435"],correct:"\u043c\u0438\u0440"},{question:"measure",variants:["\u043f\u0440\u0435\u0434\u0441\u0442\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0442\u044c","\u0437\u0430\u0440\u044f\u0436\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043c\u0435\u0440\u0430","\u043c\u0438\u0440","\u0432\u043b\u0438\u044f\u043d\u0438\u0435"],correct:"\u043c\u0435\u0440\u0430"},{question:"fly",variants:["\u043b\u0435\u0442\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0437\u0430\u0440\u044f\u0436\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043c\u0435\u0440\u0430","\u043c\u0438\u0440","\u0432\u043b\u0438\u044f\u043d\u0438\u0435"],correct:"\u043b\u0435\u0442\u0430\u0442\u044c"},{question:"weight",variants:["\u043b\u0435\u0442\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0437\u0430\u0440\u044f\u0436\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u043c\u0435\u0440\u0430","\u043c\u0438\u0440","\u043c\u0430\u0441\u0441\u0430"],correct:"\u043c\u0430\u0441\u0441\u0430"},{question:"width",variants:["\u043b\u0435\u0442\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0448\u0438\u0440\u0438\u043d\u0430","\u043c\u0435\u0440\u0430","\u043c\u0438\u0440","\u043c\u0430\u0441\u0441\u0430"],correct:"\u0448\u0438\u0440\u0438\u043d\u0430"},{question:"bottom",variants:["\u043b\u0435\u0442\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0448\u0438\u0440\u0438\u043d\u0430","\u043d\u0438\u0436\u043d\u0438\u0439","\u043c\u0438\u0440","\u043c\u0430\u0441\u0441\u0430"],correct:"\u043d\u0438\u0436\u043d\u0438\u0439"},{question:"adult",variants:["\u043b\u0435\u0442\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0448\u0438\u0440\u0438\u043d\u0430","\u043d\u0438\u0436\u043d\u0438\u0439","\u0432\u0437\u0440\u043e\u0441\u043b\u044b\u0439","\u043c\u0430\u0441\u0441\u0430"],correct:"\u0432\u0437\u0440\u043e\u0441\u043b\u044b\u0439"},{question:"worry",variants:["\u0432\u043e\u043b\u043d\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u0448\u0438\u0440\u0438\u043d\u0430","\u043d\u0438\u0436\u043d\u0438\u0439","\u0432\u0437\u0440\u043e\u0441\u043b\u044b\u0439","\u043c\u0430\u0441\u0441\u0430"],correct:"\u0432\u043e\u043b\u043d\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f"},{question:"challenge",variants:["\u0432\u043e\u043b\u043d\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u0448\u0438\u0440\u0438\u043d\u0430","\u043d\u0438\u0436\u043d\u0438\u0439","\u0432\u0437\u0440\u043e\u0441\u043b\u044b\u0439","\u0432\u044b\u0437\u043e\u0432"],correct:"\u0432\u044b\u0437\u043e\u0432"},{question:"fear",variants:["\u0432\u043e\u043b\u043d\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u0441\u0442\u0440\u0430\u0445","\u043d\u0438\u0436\u043d\u0438\u0439","\u0432\u0437\u0440\u043e\u0441\u043b\u044b\u0439","\u0432\u044b\u0437\u043e\u0432"],correct:"\u0441\u0442\u0440\u0430\u0445"},{question:"shoulder",variants:["\u0432\u043e\u043b\u043d\u043e\u0432\u0430\u0442\u044c\u0441\u044f","\u0441\u0442\u0440\u0430\u0445","\u043f\u043b\u0435\u0447\u043e","\u0432\u0437\u0440\u043e\u0441\u043b\u044b\u0439","\u0432\u044b\u0437\u043e\u0432"],correct:"\u043f\u043b\u0435\u0447\u043e"},{question:"middle",variants:["\u0441\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043d\u0438\u0439","\u0441\u0442\u0440\u0430\u0445","\u043f\u043b\u0435\u0447\u043e","\u0432\u0437\u0440\u043e\u0441\u043b\u044b\u0439","\u0432\u044b\u0437\u043e\u0432"],correct:"\u0441\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043d\u0438\u0439"},{question:"sea",variants:["\u0441\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043d\u0438\u0439","\u043c\u043e\u0440\u0435","\u043f\u043b\u0435\u0447\u043e","\u0432\u0437\u0440\u043e\u0441\u043b\u044b\u0439","\u0432\u044b\u0437\u043e\u0432"],correct:"\u043c\u043e\u0440\u0435"},{question:"dream",variants:["\u043c\u0435\u0447\u0442\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0441\u0442\u0440\u0430\u0445","\u043f\u043b\u0435\u0447\u043e","\u0432\u0437\u0440\u043e\u0441\u043b\u044b\u0439","\u0432\u044b\u0437\u043e\u0432"],correct:"\u043c\u0435\u0447\u0442\u0430\u0442\u044c"},{question:"property",variants:["\u0441\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043d\u0438\u0439","\u0441\u0442\u0440\u0430\u0445","\u043f\u043b\u0435\u0447\u043e","\u0438\u043c\u0443\u0449\u0435\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e","\u0432\u044b\u0437\u043e\u0432"],correct:"\u0438\u043c\u0443\u0449\u0435\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e"},{question:"instead",variants:["\u0441\u0440\u0435\u0434\u043d\u0438\u0439","\u0432\u043c\u0435\u0441\u0442\u043e","\u043f\u043b\u0435\u0447\u043e","\u0438\u043c\u0443\u0449\u0435\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e","\u0432\u044b\u0437\u043e\u0432"],correct:"\u0432\u043c\u0435\u0441\u0442\u043e"},{question:"improve",variants:["\u0443\u043b\u0443\u0447\u0448\u0430\u0442\u044c","\u0432\u043c\u0435\u0441\u0442\u043e","\u043f\u043b\u0435\u0447\u043e","\u0438\u043c\u0443\u0449\u0435\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e","\u0432\u044b\u0437\u043e\u0432"],correct:"\u0443\u043b\u0443\u0447\u0448\u0430\u0442\u044c"}]},y=function(t){return Object(o.jsxs)("div",{className:"alert alert-danger info",role:"alert",children:[Object(o.jsx)("h1",{children:"\u0417\u0430\u0434\u0430\u0447\u0430 \u043d\u0435 \u0432\u044b\u043f\u043e\u043b\u043d\u0435\u043d\u0430!"}),Object(o.jsx)("h2",{children:"\u041f\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0438\u043b\u044c\u043d\u044b\u0445 \u043e\u0442\u0432\u0435\u0442\u043e\u0432 ".concat(t.questNumber-1)}),Object(o.jsx)("button",{type:"button",className:"btn btn-outline-success",onClick:function(){t.startTest()},children:"\u041d\u0430\u0447\u0430\u0442\u044c \u0441\u043d\u0430\u0447\u0430\u043b\u0430"})]})},w=function(t){var r=Object(n.useState)(j(x().length)),e=Object(l.a)(r,2),a=e[0],s=e[1],c=Object(n.useState)(1),i=Object(l.a)(c,2),u=i[0],v=i[1],q=Object(n.useState)(x().length-1),h=Object(l.a)(q,2),m=h[0],O=h[1],p=Object(n.useState)(x()[a[u-1]]),f=Object(l.a)(p,2),w=f[0],N=f[1],k=Object(n.useState)(!0),T=Object(l.a)(k,2),C=T[0],E=T[1],S=Object(n.useState)(!1),F=Object(l.a)(S,2),I=F[0],L=F[1],M=Object(n.useState)(!1),H=Object(l.a)(M,2),B=H[0],D=H[1],J=function(){O(x().length-1),N(x()[a[0]]),v(1),L(!1)},P=function(){E(!0)};return Object(o.jsxs)("div",{className:"starTest",children:[C&&Object(o.jsx)(g,{gameOver:function(){D(!1),s(j(x().length)),L(!0)},state:w,finish:m,live:t.live,congratulation:function(){D(!0),s(j(x().length)),L(!0)},nextClick:function(){N(x()[a[u]]),v(u+1),E(!1),P(),O(m-1)},questNumber:u}),Object(o.jsx)(b.a,{in:I,timeout:300,classNames:"alert",unmountOnExit:!0,onEnter:function(){return E(!1)},onExited:function(){return E(!0)},children:B?Object(o.jsx)(d,{startTest:J}):Object(o.jsx)(y,{questNumber:u,startTest:J})})]})};var N=function(){return Object(o.jsx)(o.Fragment,{children:Object(o.jsxs)(c.a,{children:[Object(o.jsx)(u,{}),Object(o.jsxs)(i.c,{children:[Object(o.jsx)(i.a,{exact:!0,path:"/english-learn",component:q}),Object(o.jsx)(i.a,{exact:!0,path:"/about",component:v}),Object(o.jsx)(i.a,{exact:!0,path:"/startTestsEasy",render:function(){return Object(o.jsx)(w,{live:1})}}),Object(o.jsx)(i.a,{exact:!0,path:"/startTestsHard",render:function(){return Object(o.jsx)(w,{live:0})}})]})]})})},k=function(t){t&&t instanceof Function&&e.e(3).then(e.bind(null,47)).then((function(r){var e=r.getCLS,n=r.getFID,a=r.getFCP,s=r.getLCP,c=r.getTTFB;e(t),n(t),a(t),s(t),c(t)}))},T=e(25),C=e(21),E=e(26),S=e(22),F="DELETE_ITEM",I={},L=function(){var t=arguments.length>0&&void 0!==arguments[0]?arguments[0]:I,r=arguments.length>1?arguments[1]:void 0;switch(r.type){case F:return Object(S.a)(Object(S.a)({},t),{},{test:Object(E.a)(t.test[r.indeX].variants[r.item]=null)});default:return t}},M=Object(C.a)({englishTestReducers:L}),H=Object(C.b)(M);s.a.render(Object(o.jsx)(T.a,{store:H,children:Object(o.jsx)(N,{})}),document.getElementById("root")),k()}},[[44,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.8f649be7.chunk.js.map